<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prepares on Hugo documentation theme</title><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/</link><description>Recent content in Prepares on Hugo documentation theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Designed by [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com) &amp; Developed by [Gethugothemes](https://gethugothemes.com)</copyright><atom:link href="https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/access-key-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/access-key-management/</guid><description>Create and Manage Alert Logic Access Keys Access keys store credentials that are used to integrate external applications with the Alert Logic API. Access keys must be generated in the Alert Logic console.
To access this functionality:
In the Alert Logic console menu, click Manage, and then click Users. Scroll to the desired user account, and then click VIEW. In the account information slideout panel, click the Access Keys tab. From this page, you can generate, download, and manage your access keys.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/agent-container-fargate-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/agent-container-fargate-beta/</guid><description>Deploy the Alert Logic Agent Container for AWS Fargate (Beta) This document is intended for early-access customers. You can deploy the Alert Logic Agent Container in Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS) environments that run Amazon Web Services (AWS) Fargate.
Use these instructions for environments running Amazon ECS tasks with the Fargate launch type. To deploy the Alert Logic Agent Container for Amazon ECS tasks with the EC2 launch type, see the ECS README instead.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/agent-container-fargate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/agent-container-fargate/</guid><description>Deploy the Alert Logic Agent Container for AWS Fargate You can deploy the Alert Logic Agent Container in Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS) environments that run Amazon Web Services (AWS) Fargate.
AWS Fargate support To protect environments that use Fargate with Amazon ECS, the required method is to deploy the Alert Logic Agent Container as a sidecar in each Fargate ECS task. With this method, the Alert Logic agent can still access the network interfaces of that task.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/agent-install-automated-aws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/agent-install-automated-aws/</guid><description>Automate Alert Logic Agent Installation with AWS Systems Manager Distributor Alert Logic provides an agent that gathers data that Alert Logic must collect for analysis, such as log messages and network traffic, metadata, and host identification information.
If you have Amazon Web Services (AWS) Systems Manager managed instances, you can use AWS Systems Manager Distributor to install the Alert Logic agent on the instances. Distributor is a feature integrated with AWS Systems Manager that you can use to securely store and distribute software packages in your accounts.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/alert-logic-agent-container/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/alert-logic-agent-container/</guid><description>Install the Alert Logic Agent Container You can deploy the Alert Logic Agent Container on the following container platforms:
Amazon Web Services (AWS)
Amazon Elastic Container Service for Kubernetes (Amazon EKS) Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) Amazon ECS running AWS Fargate AWS Elastic Beanstalk for Multicontainer Docker Environments CoreOS deployed on AWS EC2 instances Docker Kubernetes deployed on AWS EC2 instances Microsoft Azure
Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) CoreOS on Azure Docker Kubernetes ACS-Engine Google Cloud Platform</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/alert-logic-agent-linux-uninstall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/alert-logic-agent-linux-uninstall/</guid><description>Uninstall the Alert Logic Agent for Linux You can uninstall the Alert Logic agent for Linux. If you have previously installed an older Linux version of an Alert Logic agent, you must uninstall that version before you install the current agent image.
Uninstall an agent RPM package To uninstall the agent RPM package:
Run the following command to locate the agent RPM package: rpm -qa | grep agent Run the following command to uninstall the agent RPM package: rpm -ev &amp;amp;lt;packageNameFromStep1&amp;amp;gt; Run the following command to delete the Alert Logic directory: rm -rf /var/alertlogic For instructions to reinstall the agent RPM package, see Install the Alert Logic Agent for Linux.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/alert-logic-agent-linux/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/alert-logic-agent-linux/</guid><description>Install the Alert Logic Agent for Linux Alert Logic provides an agent that gathers data that Alert Logic must collect for analysis, such as log messages and network traffic, as well as metadata and host identification information. You must download the agent, and then deploy it to each host you want to monitor, or collect log messages. Alert Logic provides agents for Windows and Linux hosts. For more information, see Requirements for the Alert Logic Agent.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/alert-logic-agent-windows-uninstall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/alert-logic-agent-windows-uninstall/</guid><description>Uninstall the Alert Logic Agent for Windows You can uninstall the Alert Logic agent for Windows by using Control Panel or a command prompt.
Uninstall the agent by using Control Panel To uninstall the agent by using Control Panel:
Open the Services App: To open the Run dialog box, press the Windows logo key, and then press R. Type &amp;ldquo;services.msc&amp;rdquo; in the Open field. Press Enter. Stop the Alert Logic agent service: Right-click AL Agent.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/alert-logic-agent-windows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/alert-logic-agent-windows/</guid><description>Install the Alert Logic Agent for Windows Alert Logic provides an agent that gathers data that Alert Logic must collect for analysis, such as log messages and network traffic, as well as metadata and host identification information. You must download the agent, and then deploy it to each host you want to monitor, or collect log messages. Alert Logic provides agents for Windows and Linux hosts. For more information, see Requirements for the Alert Logic Agent.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/alert-logic-physical-appliance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/alert-logic-physical-appliance/</guid><description>Install and Configure the Physical Appliance The Alert Logic physical appliance is a server that is preconfigured by Alert Logic to collect IDS data and provide Alert Logic Managed Web Application Firewall (WAF) services. Alert Logic offers two physical appliances—the Dell PowerEdge R240 and the Dell PowerEdge R640. You can use this document for either physical appliance.
Your conversations with Alert Logic representatives determine which physical appliance corresponds with your Alert Logic subscription level and best serves the goals of your organization.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/authenticated-scanning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/authenticated-scanning/</guid><description>Authenticated Scanning Alert Logic allows you to use credentials to perform host-level authenticated scanning. Using Windows or Secure Shell (SSH) credentials as part of your scans allows for more accurate vulnerability scans and lowers the number of false positive results.
Windows authenticated scanning Windows authenticated scanning is an authenticated network-based method for interrogating the target machine for missing security-related patches and updates.
To run Windows authenticated scanning, you must set up the following parameters:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/aws-cross-account-role-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/aws-cross-account-role-setup/</guid><description>AWS Cross-account Role Setup Alert Logic supports Amazon Web Services (AWS) cross-account roles. The Deployments page in the Alert Logic console allows you to create deployments for your AWS accounts. On this page, you can edit an AWS deployment name, add and edit AWS credentials to provide Alert Logic with cross-account access to those accounts, and delete deployments. For more information about deployments, see Get Started with Alert Logic Deployments.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/aws-full-permission-deployment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/aws-full-permission-deployment/</guid><description>Configure AWS Full Permission Deployment Alert Logic recommends full permission deployment, which requires the use of the recommended policy available within the Alert Logic console. This set of permissions allows Alert Logic to discover your AWS environment and automate the setup of the required AWS services.
To use full permission deployment, you must grant Alert Logic permissions to make changes to your environment (enable/modify AWS CloudTrail settings, create an Amazon SQS queue and an Amazon SNS topic, and modify permissions).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/aws-minimal-permission-deployment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/aws-minimal-permission-deployment/</guid><description>Configure AWS Minimal Permission Deployment in Manual Mode Alert Logic strongly recommends deploying with full permissions to facilitate the discovery of your AWS environment and allow Alert Logic to automate required AWS services. To learn more about full permission deployment, see Configure AWS Full Permission Deployment.
Minimal permission deployment employs the most limited privileges that still allow Alert Logic to work properly in AWS.
Minimal permission deployment allows you to set up CloudTrail in either the AWS account you want protected by Alert Logic or in a separate account with an S3 bucket to which CloudTrail is configured for centralized log collection.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/azure-benchmark-deployment-configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/azure-benchmark-deployment-configuration/</guid><description>Update your Azure Deployment for CIS Foundation Benchmarks Alert Logic requires updates to your Azure deployments to comply with Microsoft Azure Center for Internet Security (CIS) Foundation Benchmarks, an established best practices baseline configuration guideline. The update furthers your security measures by allowing Alert Logic to perform CIS benchmark checks on your deployments that expose vulnerabilities.
For more information about Microsoft Azure CIS Benchmarks, see cisecurity.org/benchmark/azure.
When you configured your Azure deployments, you created an app registration, and then used an Azure role-based access control (RBAC) to create and assign a role to that app registration in your Azure resources.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/azure-deployment-update-cis-foundation-benchmarks-user-credentials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/azure-deployment-update-cis-foundation-benchmarks-user-credentials/</guid><description>Update your Azure Deployment with User Credentials for CIS Foundation Benchmarks Alert Logic requires updates to your Azure deployments to comply with Microsoft Azure Center for Internet Security (CIS) Foundation Benchmarks, an established guideline for baseline configuration best practices. The update furthers your security measures by allowing Alert Logic to perform CIS benchmark checks on your deployments that expose vulnerabilities.
For more information about Microsoft Azure CIS Benchmarks, see cisecurity.org/benchmark/azure.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/azure-event-hubs-log-collector/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/azure-event-hubs-log-collector/</guid><description>Alert Logic Log Collector for Microsoft Azure Event Hubs Microsoft Azure Event Hubs is a data streaming platform and event ingestion service that can receive and process millions of events per second. Alert Logic allows you to configure Event Hubs to collect your Azure logs and forward them to Alert Logic.
To grant Alert Logic permission to access Event Hubs for log collection, you must have:
Microsoft Azure account with Active Directory tenant privileges Alert Logic user account Alert Logic access key Alert Logic recommends that you create Azure deployments in the Alert Logic console for each Azure subscription you want to use to collect logs from Event Hubs.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/azure-rbac-role-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/azure-rbac-role-setup/</guid><description>Configure App Registration and RBAC for Microsoft Azure Resources For Alert Logic to protect your Azure deployments, you must configure Microsoft Azure resources to allow Alert Logic to monitor your assets. All procedures require administrative permission in the Azure portal.
You must create an app registration, and then use Azure role-based access control (RBAC) to create and assign a role to that app registration.
To comply with Center for Internet Security (CIS) benchmarks for Microsoft Azure, an established best practices baseline configuration guideline, you must grant certain permissions to access Microsoft Graph and Azure Key Vault.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/centos08-update-legacy-aws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/centos08-update-legacy-aws/</guid><description>CentOS Version 8 Update for AWS Legacy Customers CentOS announced the end of life for their version 6 operating system. This means CentOS will no longer provide security patches, vulnerabilities, or bug fixes for version 6. As a result, Alert Logic is helping customers update all Alert Logic appliances running on operating system CentOS version 6 to the current and supported version 8.
As Alert Logic transitions all customers to CentOS 8, Alert Logic will continue maintain necessary security updates for CentOS version 6 to ensure all customers remain secure.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/centos08-update-legacy-ova/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/centos08-update-legacy-ova/</guid><description>CentOS Version 8 Update for Legacy Customers using OVA CentOS announced the end of life for their version 6 operating system. This means CentOS will no longer provide security patches, vulnerabilities, or bug fixes for version 6. As a result, Alert Logic is helping customers update all Alert Logic appliances running on operating system CentOS version 6 to the current and supported version 8.
As Alert Logic transitions all customers to CentOS 8, Alert Logic will continue maintain necessary security updates for CentOS version 6 to ensure all customers remain secure.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/centos08-update-mdr-aws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/centos08-update-mdr-aws/</guid><description>CentOS Version 8 Update for AWS MDR Customers CentOS announced the end of life for their version 6 operating system. This means CentOS will no longer provide security patches, vulnerabilities, or bug fixes for version 6. As a result, Alert Logic is helping customers update all Alert Logic appliances running on operating system CentOS version 6 to the current and supported version 8.
As Alert Logic transitions all customers to CentOS 8, Alert Logic will continue maintain necessary security updates for CentOS version 6 to ensure all customers remain secure.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/centos08-update-mdr-ova/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/centos08-update-mdr-ova/</guid><description>CentOS Version 8 Update for MDR Customers using OVA CentOS announced the end of life for their version 6 operating system. This means CentOS will no longer provide security patches, vulnerabilities, or bug fixes for version 6. As a result, Alert Logic is helping customers update all Alert Logic appliances running on operating system CentOS version 6 to the current and supported version 8.
As Alert Logic transitions all customers to CentOS 8, Alert Logic will continue maintain necessary security updates for CentOS version 6 to ensure all customers remain secure.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/centos08-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/centos08-update/</guid><description>CentOS Version 8 Update CentOS has announced the end of life for their version 6 and 8 operating systems. This means CentOS will no longer provide security patches, vulnerabilities, or bug fixes for these operating systems. As a result, Alert Logic is helping customers update all Alert Logic appliances running on out-of-date operating systems.
Updating to the currently supported operating system requires two steps:
Step 1 needs to be completed by you, the customer.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/collect-syslog-no-agent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/collect-syslog-no-agent/</guid><description>How to collect syslog for an appliance without the agent Syslog forwarding is used to send log messages to the Alert Logic Log Manager. The device is then listed on the Sources screen under Collection in the Alert Logic console.
**Consider the following scenarios: **
Existing central syslog server If you already have a central syslog server, you can forward syslog traffic to a virtual appliance or a physical appliance.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/iam-role-creation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/iam-role-creation/</guid><description>Configure IAM Role for Amazon Web Services (AWS) Alert Logic supports Amazon Web Services (AWS) cross-account roles, which allow you to grant Alert Logic third-party access to your AWS accounts. In the AWS console, you can create multiple IAM roles, which grant different permissions based on the policy document you use to create the role.
Create a cross-account access role Alert Logic recommends that you configure your deployment with full permissions, which allows Alert Logic to discover your AWS environment and automate the setup of the required AWS services.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/manage-user-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/manage-user-account/</guid><description>Manage Your User Account The Alert Logic Users page allows you to manage user account settings, such as your name, contact information, and password.
User accounts with the administrator role can manage the details for other users in their organization. For more information about creating and managing other accounts, see Customer Accounts, User Accounts, and User Roles.
Update your user account details For your user account, you can manage your contact information and your password.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/mfa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/mfa/</guid><description>Multi-factor Authentication Multi-factor authentication (MFA) provides additional account security through a required authentication code that you must enter, in addition to your Alert Logic account credentials, when you log into the Alert Logic console. If your account requires MFA, you must set up a device, such as a smart phone or a tablet, to generate the required authentication code to sign into the Alert Logic console. Alert Logic supports time-based one-time password (TOTP) apps, like Google Authenticator, Authy, or 1Password.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/office365-log-collector/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/office365-log-collector/</guid><description>Set Up Collection of Microsoft Office 365 Logs The instructions in this document are for an older setup of the Microsoft Office 365 log collector. If this is your first time setting up Microsoft Office 365 collectors, see Configure Microsoft Office 365 Log Collector. If you previously installed the older version of Office 365 and want to update using the Alert Logic console, see Set Up Collection of Microsoft Office 365 Logs.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/physical-appliance-change-ip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/physical-appliance-change-ip/</guid><description>Change the IP Address of a Physical Appliance Alert Logic ships appliances with a preconfigured network IP address. If you need to add or update an appliance IP address, you must use the network configuration utility Alert Logic provides for this purpose. Alert Logic suggests you contact Technical Support for guidance:
In the US, call (877) 484-8383, and then select option 2. In the EU, call +44 (0) 203 011 5533, and then select option 2.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/remote-log-collector-linux/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/remote-log-collector-linux/</guid><description>Install the Remote Collector for Linux A remote collector collects, compresses, and encrypts log data from the configured remote machines to send directly to Alert Logic. For more information on the system requirements for a remote collector, see Requirements for the Alert Logic Remote Collector.
A remote collector can only collect syslog data.
A remote collector is useful because:
A remote collector can be installed on a Windows machine or a Linux machine.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/remote-log-collector-windows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/remote-log-collector-windows/</guid><description>Install the Remote Collector for Windows A remote collector collects, compresses, and encrypts log data from the configured remote machines to send directly to Alert Logic. For more information on the system requirements for a remote collector, see Requirements for the Alert Logic Remote Collector.
Remote collectors only support syslog collection.
A remote collector is useful because:
A remote collector can be installed on a Windows machine or a Linux machine.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/settings/</guid><description>Settings Menu The documentation below describes the previous version of the Alert Logic console, which was recently updated. The Settings Menu will be phased out in early 2020, but all functionality will remain. For information about new link locations, see Get Started with the Alert Logic Console.
Click the Settings icon () to get to the Settings menu. The menu includes support information, integrations configuration, user settings, notifications, service status, vulnerability updates, PCI scanning, PCI scan disputes, and the link to sign out of the Alert Logic console.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/unique-registration-key/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/unique-registration-key/</guid><description>Access Unique Registration Keys for Data Center Deployments Each network configured in your Data Center deployments has a Unique Registration Key. During the installation process for the Alert Logic agent, virtual appliance, and remote collectors, you must provide the key when prompted. The Unique Registration Key specifies where the agent, appliance, or collector is located.
To access your Unique Registration Key:
In the Alert Logic console, open the relevant Data Center deployment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/users-roles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/users-roles/</guid><description>Customer Accounts, User Accounts, and User Roles The account provisioning process includes the creation of a customer account for your organization and a user account, with the Administrator role applied, under that customer account. Users in your organization with administrator privileges can log into the Alert Logic console to create and manage the user accounts required for your organization.
For information about managing your own user account, see Manage Your User Account.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/virtual-appliance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/virtual-appliance/</guid><description>Install and Configure the Virtual Appliance The main use for an Alert Logic virtual appliance is for network IDS analysis and scanning in VMWare deployments.
If you have experience with VMWare management tools and virtual machine installation, you can install a virtual appliance into your environment to collect network traffic and data.
The instructions below are not a complete guide to configure vSphere or virtual data centers. VMWare offers more information regarding vSphere.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/webhooks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/prepare/webhooks/</guid><description>Security. Compliance. Cloud. * [Home](../home.md)
* [GET STARTED](../home.md#get-started)
* [REQUIREMENTS](../home.md#requirements)
* [INSTALLATION](../home.md#installation)
* [PRODUCT GUIDES](../home.md#product-guides)
* [API](https://docs.alertlogic.com/developer/)
* [RELEASE NOTES](../home.md#release-notes)
Webhooks The webhooks integration provides the ability to send alert notifications to any public-facing web server configured to handle HTTP callbacks. Webhooks allow Alert Logic products to send real-time data directly to a third-party application, such as your ticketing system or instant messaging system, rather than to one or more email addresses or groups.</description></item></channel></rss>