<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Analyse on Hugo documentation theme</title><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/</link><description>Recent content in Analyse on Hugo documentation theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Designed by [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com) &amp; Developed by [Gethugothemes](https://gethugothemes.com)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 11:02:05 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/advanced-search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/advanced-search/</guid><description>Perform Advanced Searches The advanced search feature allows you to create complex queries that can combine with selected filters to further refine your incident search results. To access the advanced search feature, click advanced search under the search bar (add link here).
In the advanced search field, type a query statement using available fields and operators. If needed, you can use subsequent search fields to add OR statements and create a search that tests for multiple conditions.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/coverage-health-csh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/coverage-health-csh/</guid><description>Coverage and Health The Coverage and Health dashboard provides insight into your entitlement usage and statuses in your environment. Use this dashboard to improve network protection, fix configuration issues, and support optimization efforts in your environment. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Current count of open configuration exposures in each threat level. Status of networks in healthy and unhealthy categories. Status of appliance collection in healthy and unhealthy categories.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/authentication-management-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/authentication-management-security/</guid><description>Authentication Management Security The Authentication Management Security dashboard provides a summary of your authentication security activity in your environment. Use this dashboard to gain insights into your user authentication attempts and login activity in your environment. To learn more about authentication security incidents, see Authentication Application Security Incidents.
Access the Authentication Management Security dashboard To access the Authentication Management Security dashboard, in the Dashboards page, click the drop-down menu on the top left to see the list of available dashboards, and then click Authentication Management Security.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/authentication-management-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/authentication-management-summary/</guid><description>Authentication Management Summary The Authentication Management Summary dashboard provides a summary of your authentication management application security incidents in your environment. Use this dashboard to gain insights into your management efforts of your authentication security incidents, and focus your resources on threats and anomalies in user login trends and activities in your environment. To learn more about authentication security incidents, see Authentication Application Security Incidents.
Access the Authentication Management Summary dashboard To access the Authentication Management Summary dashboard, in the Dashboards page, click the drop-down menu on the top left to see the list of available dashboards, and then click ** Authentication Management Summary**.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/coverage-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/coverage-health/</guid><description>Coverage and Health Dashboard The Coverage and Health dashboard provides insight into statuses in your environment and your entitlement usage. Use this dashboard to improve network protection, fix configuration issues, and support optimization efforts in your environment. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Network and collection statuses Open configuration exposures Unprotected node count The Coverage and Health Dashboard is a new dashboard that is part of the Dashboard feature.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/endpoint-protection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/endpoint-protection/</guid><description>Endpoint Protection Dashboard The Endpoint Protection dashboard provides a summary of your endpoint activity in your environment. Use this dashboard to gain insights into your endpoint activity, learn about attack patterns, and analyze the effectiveness of your current threat and incident management process. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Endpoint statuses Active platforms Malware attacks detected Most attacked users and endpoints Top attack types Blocked attacks Responses to attacks The Endpoint Protection is a new dashboard that is part of the Dashboard feature.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/file-integrity-monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/file-integrity-monitoring/</guid><description>File Integrity Monitoring Dashboard The File Integrity Monitoring dashboard provides a summary of your file monitoring activity and issues found in your environment. Use this dashboard to gain insights into your file monitoring scope and status, focus your resources on specific systems or users that may need further investigation, and identify patterns or anomalies in your environment. To learn more about File Integrity Monitoring (FIM), see File Integrity Monitoring .</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/firewall-log-security-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/firewall-log-security-dashboard/</guid><description>Firewall Log Security Analysis Dashboard The Firewall Log Security Analysis dashboard provides insights into the firewall security incidents generated from analyzing firewall logs in your environment. Use this dashboard to quickly identify the types of firewall incidents that were detected, analyze the effectiveness of your current firewall incident response efforts, and learn about emerging threats. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Count and percentages of incident threat level categories Count of incidents in each classification Trend of firewall security incidents over time List of source internal hosts with the most incidents List of targeted internal hosts with the most incidents The Firewall Log Security Analysis Dashboard is only offered to Managed Detection and Response Professional customers.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/firewall-log-traffic-analysis-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/firewall-log-traffic-analysis-dashboard/</guid><description>Firewall Log Traffic Analysis Dashboard The Firewall Log Traffic Analysis dashboard provides insights into the firewall traffic connections found from analyzing firewall logs in your environment. Use this dashboard to identify the types of connections that were detected, trends that require further investigations, and learn about emerging threats. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Trend of firewall traffic over time Top protocol connections and application connections Trends of connection by top protocols and applications List of connections Maps of established and missed connection locations The Firewall Log Traffic Analysis Dashboard is only offered to Managed Detection and Response Professional customers.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/firewall-log-volume-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/firewall-log-volume-dashboard/</guid><description>Firewall Log Volume Analysis Dashboard The Firewall Log Volume Analysis dashboard provides insights into the volume of firewall log messages, firewall security incidents and observations in your environment. Use this dashboard to quickly identify patterns, trends and anomalies that require immediate response or further investigations. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Change amount and percentage of firewall log messages, observations and incidents Trends for firewall log messages, observations, and incidents Alert Logic identifies relevant security information derived from one or multiple sources from the log data collected, which are referred to as observations.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/managed-accounts-health-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/managed-accounts-health-summary/</guid><description>Managed Accounts Health Summary Dashboard The Managed Accounts Health Summary dashboard summarizes and provides insights into the health status of the accounts you manage. The visuals include information about unhealthy appliances and agents, unprotected nodes, missing agents, and configuration remediations. Use this dashboard to quickly identify unhealthy accounts, patterns, and anomalies that require immediate response or further investigation monitor your accounts and make necessary changes. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/managed-accounts/managed-accounts-health-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/managed-accounts/managed-accounts-health-summary/</guid><description>Managed Accounts Health Summary Dashboard The Managed Accounts Health Summary dashboard summarizes and provides insights into the health status of the accounts you manage from the previous day. The visuals include information about on unhealthy appliances and agents, unprotected nodes, missing agents, and configuration remediations. Use this dashboard to quickly identify unhealthy accounts, patterns, and anomalies that require immediate response or further investigation monitor your accounts and make necessary changes. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/managed-accounts/managed-accounts-security-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/managed-accounts/managed-accounts-security-summary/</guid><description>Managed Accounts Security Summary Dashboard The Managed Accounts Security Summary dashboard provides insights into the recent security status of the accounts you manage. The visuals includes information about incidents, vulnerabilities, Threat Risk Index (TRI) scores, and security remediations. Use this dashboard to quickly identify risky accounts, patterns, and anomalies that require immediate response or further investigations. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Total accounts with critical and high incidents Change amount and percentage of current high severity vulnerabilities, the average TRI score, and the average age of vulnerabilities Scorecards of incidents and vulnerabilities data for each account Top accounts with the most incidents, highest TRI scores, most vulnerabilities, and most security remediations The Managed Accounts Security Summary Dashboard is an additional dashboard only offered to partners and customers with managed accounts.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/navigation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/navigation/</guid><description>Managed Detection and Response Navigation Menu Updates In early 2020, Alert Logic released a new navigation system for the Alert Logic console, as well as a set of interactive, visual dashboards that summarize data, product capabilities, and the state of your environment. For more information, see Dashboards.
The new navigation menu The new navigation menu is located on the left side of the page under a menu icon (), and the options are nested.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/threat-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/threat-summary/</guid><description>Threat Summary Dashboard The Threat Summary dashboard provides visibility into threats and incidents in your environment. Use this dashboard to gain insights into the types of incidents that were detected, analyze the effectiveness of your current incident response efforts, and learn about emerging threats. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Open incidents Incident threat levels and trend Classification of your incidents Countries where incidents originate Most attacked deployments and hosts Top attackers Peer incident classification comparison The Threat Summary is a new dashboard that is part of the Dashboard feature.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/tri-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/tri-summary/</guid><description>Threat Risk Index Summary The Threat Risk Index (TRI) Summary dashboard provides insights into the recent TRI scores of your environment, including the average TRI score and trends, vulnerabilities changes, last scanned asset changes, and TRI scores by assets. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Current average TRI score Trend of TRI scores Current total vulnerabilities count with change amount and percentage Current last scanned assets count with change amount and percentage TRI scores for deployments, and VPCs/networks Most vulnerable hosts by TRI score Top vulnerabilities by TRI score For more about how Alert Logic calculates TRI scores, see Threat Risk Index Score Factors.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/vulnerability-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/vulnerability-summary/</guid><description>Vulnerability Summary Dashboard The Vulnerability Summary dashboard provides visibility into vulnerable software and cloud infrastructure in your environment. Use this dashboard to gain insights into the effectiveness of your current vulnerability management efforts, learn about new vulnerabilities and emerging threats, help prioritize your remediation plans, and focus on specific areas in your environment. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Vulnerability, exposure, and remediation counts Vulnerability severity trends Vulnerabilities by threat levels Vulnerabilities by deployments Top security remediations Most seen exposures Most vulnerable hosts The Vulnerability Summary is a new dashboard that is part of the Dashboard feature.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/web-log-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboard/web-log-analytics/</guid><description>Web Log Analytics Dashboard The Web Log Analytics (WLA) dashboard provides visibility into threats, incidents, and observations detected from your WLA instance in your environment. Use this dashboard to gain insights into the types of incidents detected in your environment, analyze the effectiveness of your current incident response efforts, and learn about emerging threats. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Count of open WLA incidents List of most seen attackers List of most attacked hosts Countries where WLA incidents originate Web attack trends Top observations The Web Log Analytics (WLA) Dashboard is only offered to Managed Detection and Response Professional customers.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboards-csh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboards-csh/</guid><description>About Dashboards Dashboards introduces interactive, visual dashboards that summarize data, product capabilities, and the state of your environment. These dashboards are being released together with an easy way to navigate through the Alert Logic console.
Dashboards allows you to easily view pertinent information in visuals that feed from live data in your environment. Most visuals allow you to click items to view the source of the data in the visual. This allows you to drill down further into issues immediately on the corresponding page in the Alert Logic console, and streamline your response actions.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/dashboards/</guid><description>Dashboards Dashboards is a new feature that introduces interactive, visual dashboards that summarize data, product capabilities, and the state of your environment. These dashboards are being released together with an easy way to navigate through the Alert Logic console.
Dashboards allows you to easily view pertinent information in visuals that feed from live data in your environment. Most visuals allow you to click items to view the source of the data in the visual.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/endpoint-incidents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/endpoint-incidents/</guid><description>Endpoint Security Incidents Alert Logic can detect and generate endpoint incidents from log data collected from third-party endpoint application resources. Alert Logic collects log data through endpoint integrations. Endpoint security incidents enhances your security content by providing greater visibility into threats in your environment.
Security incidents are generated when suspicious events are detected that require attention to maintain your security posture, achieve regulatory compliance, or both. Alert Logic organizes the incidents by threat level and classification type on your Incidents page.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/endpoint-protection-csh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/endpoint-protection-csh/</guid><description>Endpoint Protection The Endpoint Protection dashboard provides a summary of your endpoint activity in your environment. Use this dashboard to gain insights into your endpoint activity, learn about attack patterns, and analyze the effectiveness of your current threat and incident management process. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Current count of endpoints that are on, off, or showing up with an error. Current count of endpoints that are up-to-date or out-of-date.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/exposures-csh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/exposures-csh/</guid><description>About Exposures The Exposure page provides a list of exposures, details about the exposure, evidence, affected assets, and a list of remediations to resolve an exposure, or a group of exposures. Use this information to analyze and address exposures found in your environment.
Threat Levels Exposures uses icons to help you identify the threat levels of an exposure. See the threat level categories below:
High Medium Low Info Category There are two types of exposures category—security and configuration that Alert Logic lists in the Exposures page.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/exposures-preview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/exposures-preview/</guid><description>Exposures Exposures has replaced the Remediations page as part of Dashboards. Exposures has the same functionality as Remediations, but with improvements.
The Exposures page, listed under Respond in the Alert Logic console, provides you with the information you need to analyze and address exposures in your environment. The page lists exposures found in your deployments and provides details about the exposure, evidence, and affected assets. The page also lists remediations to resolve an exposure or a group of exposures.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/exposures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/exposures/</guid><description>Exposures Exposures has replaced the Remediations page as part of Dashboards. Exposures has the same functionality as Remediations, but with improvements.
The Health page lists exposures related to configuration or connection problems that disrupt access to Alert Logic product capabilities. For more information, see Health.
The Exposures page, listed under Respond in the Alert Logic console, provides you with the information you need to analyze and address exposures in your environment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/extended-endpoint-protection-landing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/extended-endpoint-protection-landing/</guid><description>Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection Documentation Resources This documentation is intended for customers who are part of the early release of Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection.
About Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection
Get Started with Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection
Requirements for Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection
Deploy Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection
Test Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection
Manage Endpoints
Apply an Override
Uninstall Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/extended-endpoint-protection/investigate-event/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/extended-endpoint-protection/investigate-event/</guid><description>Investigate an Extended Endpoint Protection Event Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection enables you to easily triage, investigate, and take action on event alerts.Alert Logic groups similar events based on common path or common hash, to avoid individually triaging events.
Event blocking and detection Extended Endpoint Protection constantly monitors your endpoints for suspicious activity, and blocks suspicious processes when it identifies them. This identified suspicious activity is called an event. When an event is blocked, Extended Endpoint Protection automatically stops the process.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/extended-endpoint-protection/isolate-endpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/extended-endpoint-protection/isolate-endpoint/</guid><description>Isolate an Endpoint Delete this text and replace it with your own content.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/extended-endpoint-protection/quarantine-files/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/extended-endpoint-protection/quarantine-files/</guid><description>Quarantine and Delete Files In addition to automatically stopping malicious processes, Extended Endpoint Protection can quarantine malicious executables on the endpoint. Quarantining moves the file to a quarantine location on the device and encrypts the file so that end users cannot make further attempt to access and execute it. You can manually quarantine files related to an event or enable automatic quarantine to enable Extended Endpoint Protection to automatically place files in quarantine.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/firewall-incidents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/firewall-incidents/</guid><description>Firewall Incidents and Log Configuration Alert Logic can detect and generate firewall security incidents and observations from log data collected from third-party firewall application resources. Alert Logic collects log data through passive syslog forwarding from the firewall application. Firewall security incidents and observations enhances your security content value for greater visibility into threats in your environment.
Firewall security incidents are generated when suspicious events are detected that require attention to maintain your security posture, achieve regulatory compliance, or both.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/health-preview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/health-preview/</guid><description>Health The Health page, listed under Respond in the Alert Logic console, provides detailed information about your environment to ensure that your deployments are configured correctly. The Health page provides the information you need to analyze and respond to health exposures in your environment. Health exposures result from configuration or connection problems that disrupt access to Alert Logic product capabilities.
You can access a filtered Health page that shows you relevant issues in your deployments from links in visuals in the Coverage and Health Dashboard.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/health/</guid><description>Health The Health page, listed under Respond in the Alert Logic console, provides detailed information about your environment to ensure that your deployments are configured correctly. The Health page provides the information you need to analyze and respond to health exposures in your environment. Health exposures result from configuration or connection problems that disrupt access to Alert Logic product capabilities.
You can access a filtered Health page that shows you relevant issues in your deployments from links in visuals in the Coverage and Health Dashboard.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/incidents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/incidents/</guid><description>Incidents Alert Logic released an upgraded version of the Incidents page with enhanced features. You can switch between the updated Incidents page and the existing Incidents page by using the toggle icon () on the upper-right side of the page. For more information, see Incidents Upgrade .
The Alert Logic console displays information about incidents, how to use that information to manage and close incidents, and how to secure your environments.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-message-search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-message-search/</guid><description>Search: Log Messages Alert Logic is offering an improved version of the Log Search feature. To learn more about this feature, see Get Started with Search.
The Log Search feature in the Alert Logic console allows you to create SQL-like searches and aggregations that can help you find and organize log messages most relevant to your investigation. For example, to investigate which users are causing the most failed logins, you can search for log messages that have been parsed as &amp;ldquo;Windows Login Failed&amp;rdquo; and then aggregate the search results by “User Name” and “Src Host.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-review-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-review-upgrade/</guid><description>Machine Learning Log Review Upgrade Alert Logic is upgrading the Log Review process with new machine learning algorithms, which allows Alert Logic to deliver a higher level of security value. The Machine Learning Log Review algorithms can automatically detect many log-based anomaly types based on unique patterns and trends learned from your organization.
The Machine Learning Log Review output consist of anomalies generated from the machine learning based detection that are delivered as information-level incidents in the Incidents page.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search-beta/help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search-beta/help/</guid><description>Search Help Fields The Alert Logic console provides a help library of search templates and fields to help you create effective log searches that address the security concerns and goals for your organization. You can then save your searches for later use with the Save Search feature.
About search templates You have access to all the search fields in the help library. When you use a search template, you must substitute the placeholder text with values relevant to your search.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search-beta/log-search-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search-beta/log-search-beta/</guid><description>Log Search This document is intended for early-access customers and is continually being updated as the Log Search feature is finalized.
The new Log Search experience in the Alert Logic console is intended to allow you to perform basic and advance searches for different log messages data types that can help you find and organize messages most relevant to your investigation. The Log Search page is composed of Simple Mode and Expert Mode.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search-beta/save-schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search-beta/save-schedule/</guid><description>Saved and Schedule Searches Alert Logic saves your recent executed log searches and allows you to save and schedule any log search for frequent use. You must successfully run the search to be able to save and schedule a search. The Saved Searches feature lists all recent executed searches, and recent scheduled searches. You can also view scheduled search results or export them to a CSV file.
Save log searches If the security goals for your organization require you to run specific searches more than once, you can create a saved search so you can easily find and run the search in the future.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search-beta/schedule-searches/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search-beta/schedule-searches/</guid><description>Schedule Search Notification The Log Search page in the Alert Logic console allows you to perform basic and advance searches for different log messages data types that can help you find and organize messages most relevant to your investigation. You can schedule a weekly or monthly log searches for your different data types, and be notified when the search is complete. The search and notification can help you keep records and track any changes.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search-save-schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search-save-schedule/</guid><description>Create Saved and Scheduled Log Searches You can save and schedule any search for frequent use. To ensure every saved search runs correctly, the Alert Logic console does not allow you to search or save a search until you enter at least one valid search statement in the search bar. Alert Logic lists all saved searches, and their corresponding groups, created by users in your customer account, and you can execute, edit, and create templates from those searches.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/analyze-log-messages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/analyze-log-messages/</guid><description>Work with Log Messages Alert Logic is offering an improved version of the Log Search feature. To learn more about this feature, see Get Started with Search.
After you perform a log message search, you can view the details of log messages that appear in the search results. Click a message to:
View a summary of the log message View the log source properties Bookmark a message, flagging it for investigation until you run another search Add filters or tokens to the query ran previously to refine results Export the log message summary to a CSV file Create a manual incident from the message Open a log message Select a log message, and then click Open to view the details of the selected log message in a separate browser tab.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/complex-log-search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/complex-log-search/</guid><description>Create Complex Log Searches Alert Logic is offering an improved version of the Log Search feature. To learn more about this feature, see Get Started with Search.
The Alert Logic Log Search feature provides WHERE and SELECT fields that allow you to create SQL-like searches and aggregations to narrow and organize the list of search results. You can use the Search Assistant to choose search and aggregation criteria and their available operators.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/import-export-search-query/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/import-export-search-query/</guid><description>Import and Export Search Queries Alert Logic is offering an improved version of the Log Search feature. To learn more about this feature, see Get Started with Search.
If you need to share search queries with specific users, or store a search query privately for later use, you can use the Import and Export Search Query feature. An exported search query contains query details saved as a JSON file for storage and for ease of sharing electronically.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/log-search-examples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/log-search-examples/</guid><description>Examples of Common Log Message Searches Alert Logic is offering an improved version of the Log Search feature. To learn more about this feature, see Get Started with Search.
The following examples illustrate a few common log searches. You can copy the search and projection statements, and then substitute log message objects with your own to create searches relevant to your organization and its security goals.
Aggregate search results by log message type The following search and projection returns a list of all log message types, grouped by message type, and listed in descending order:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/log-search-json/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/log-search-json/</guid><description>Parsed JSON Log Search and Examples Alert Logic is offering an improved version of the Log Search feature. To learn more about this feature, see Get Started with Search.
Parsed JSON searching is built into the Log Search feature and allows you to search on fields from any JSON log. You can use JSONPath queries, parsed token names, or a combination of both to aggregate and filter log messages received in parsed JSON format.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/save-schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/save-schedule/</guid><description>Create Saved and Scheduled Log Searches Alert Logic is offering an improved version of the Log Search feature. To learn more about this feature, see Get Started with Search.
You can save and schedule any log search for frequent use. To ensure every saved search runs correctly, the Alert Logic console does not allow you to save a search until you enter at least one valid search statement in the search bar and successfully run the search.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/templates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/log-search/templates/</guid><description>Create and Manage Search Templates Alert Logic is offering an improved version of the Log Search feature. To learn more about this feature, see Get Started with Search.
The Alert Logic console provides a library of search templates to help you create effective log searches that address the security concerns and goals for your organization. The Alert Logic console allows user accounts with the Administrator role to create and manage search templates to supplement the template libraries for their customer accounts and the customer accounts they manage.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-results/adjust-settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-results/adjust-settings/</guid><description>Adjust Scan Settings You can adjust scan settings for specific assets from the Topology page in the Alert Logic console. The Topology page organizes your assets in an interactive diagram that you can filter and customize. For more information, see Topology.
Adjustments you can make to scans from the Topology page include:
Manage your credentials Adjust scan performance Scan Now Manage your credentials You can add credentials to your assets to use with internal vulnerability scans on the Topology page.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-results/agent-based-scan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-results/agent-based-scan/</guid><description>Agent-Based Scanning Agent-based scanning enables users to leverage the vulnerability assessment coverage of authenticated network scanning without the need to manage credentials and with a reduction in network traffic and impact.
State Monitor—
OSQuery—
OVALdi—
Upgrades to the scanning experience The agent-based scan upgrade improves the efficiency, accuracy, and usability of Alert Logic vulnerability scanning features.
No Credential Management Agent-based scanning does not require credential management. Users of authenticated network scans had to configure access and manage credentials for assets and networks.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-results/analyze-results/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-results/analyze-results/</guid><description>Analyze Scan Results You can use scan results to access valuable vulnerability information about your networks, including historical trends and current details. Reviewing the data helps to identify issues you can address to improve your security posture. You can review scan results and their outcomes in different pages in the Alert Logic console:
View legacy scan results View vulnerability reports View scan schedule breakdown reports View and remediate exposures detected by vulnerability scans View legacy scan results If you were subscribed to the previous version of Alert Logic products, you can view your legacy scan results from the Settings menu.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-results/schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-results/schedules/</guid><description>Manage Scan Schedules Alert Logic performs scans on all assets in your deployments. When you create a deployment, Alert Logic automatically creates default scan schedules to perform external and internal vulnerability scans on all non-excluded assets and ports that vary according to deployment type. A default discovery scan schedule also finds new assets in Data Center deployments.
You can also schedule when you want to perform specific scans. From the Scan Schedules page in the Alert Logic console, you can edit the default schedule and create additional schedules for all or selected assets and ports within the scope of protection of the deployment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-results/upgrade-agent-based-scanning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-results/upgrade-agent-based-scanning/</guid><description>Upgrade Scans with Agent-based scanning This document is intended for early-access customers, and it is updated as agent-based scanning features are enhanced. Alert Logic is upgrading vulnerability scanning by adding OSQuery and OVAL scan components to the existing Alert Logic agent.
Upgrades to Scanning Experience The agent-based scan will improve the efficacy and usability of Alert Logic vulnerability scanning features:
Credential Management: Users of credentialed network scans had to manage credentials for assets and networks.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-scan-results-preview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-scan-results-preview/</guid><description>Manage Scans and Scan Results The documentation below describes the new version of the Scan Scheduling feature in the Alert Logic console, which will become available in August 2020.
Alert Logic performs scans on all assets in your deployments. When you create a new deployment, Alert Logic automatically creates default scan schedules to perform external and internal vulnerability scans on all non-excluded assets and ports that vary according to deployment type.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-scan-results/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-and-scan-results/</guid><description>Manage Scans and Scan Results Alert Logic performs scans on all assets in your deployments. When you create a new deployment, Alert Logic automatically creates default scan schedules to perform external and internal vulnerability scans on all non-excluded assets and ports that vary according to deployment type. Alert Logic also creates a default discovery scan schedule to find new assets in Data Center deployments. You can schedule when to perform specific scans for all or selected assets and ports.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-results/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/manage-scans-results/</guid><description>How to work with scans and scan results You can access detailed information about network and host vulnerabilities discovered during internal and external scans from the Scans tab on the Scans page in the Alert Logic console. From the Scans tab, you can create new scans, edit existing scan definitions, and view scan results.
For information about PCI scans, see Manage PCI Scans.
Access Alert Logic scans You can access most scan-related features from the Scans page in the Alert Logic console.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/remediations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/remediations/</guid><description>Remediations Remediations has been deprecated and replaced as part of Dashboards. The information available on the Remediations page is available in Exposures.
The Remediations page displays the number and types of exposures in the protected deployment, and provides you with information about the exposure, including color-coded threat level, evidence, and recommendations to address the exposure.
The Remediations Summary and the Remediations List, under the Remediations tab in the Alert Logic console provide you with the information you need to analyze and address issues in your environment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/azure-foundation-benchmark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/azure-foundation-benchmark/</guid><description>CIS Microsoft Azure Foundation Benchmark CIS Microsoft Azure Foundation Benchmark report provides an assessment of how your environment conforms to configuration guidelines developed by Center for Internet Security (CIS) experts. Alert Logic performs a series of benchmark checks on your Azure deployments to display the statuses of the checks for each section.
For more information about Microsoft Azure CIS Benchmarks, see cisecurity.org/benchmark/azure.
For customers who are configuring an Azure deployment for the first time, or customers who have Azure deployments but do not have an Azure app registration set up, see Configure App Registration and RBAC for Microsoft Azure Resources.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/cis-aws-foundation-benchmark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/cis-aws-foundation-benchmark/</guid><description>CIS AWS Foundation Benchmark CIS Amazon Web Services (AWS) Foundation Benchmark report provides an assessment of how your environment conforms to configuration guidelines developed by Center for Internet Security (CIS) experts. Alert Logic performs a series of benchmark checks on your AWS deployments to display the statuses of the checks for each section.
For more information about AWS CIS Benchmarks, see cisecurity.org/benchmark/amazon_web_services.
To access the AWS Foundation Benchmark report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/gdpr-article-25-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/gdpr-article-25-data-protection/</guid><description>GDPR Article 25: Data Protection by Design and by Default The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements outlined by GDPR.
The GDPR Article 25: Data Protection by Design and by Default report describes and provides access to features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with GDPR Article 25.
To access the GDPR Article 25: Data Protection by Design and by Default report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/gdpr-article-32-security-of-processing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/gdpr-article-32-security-of-processing/</guid><description>GDPR Article 32: Security of Processing The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements outlined by GDPR.
The GDPR Article 32: Data Protection by Design and by Default report describes and provides access to features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with GDPR Article 32.
To access the GDPR Article 32: Security of Processing report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/gdpr-article-33-notification-personal-data-breach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/gdpr-article-33-notification-personal-data-breach/</guid><description>GDPR Article 33: Notification of Personal Data Breach The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements outlined by GDPR.
The GDPR Article 33: Notification of Personal Data Breach report provides access to features in the Alert Logic console that help you demonstrate compliance with GDPR Article 33.
To access the Article 33: Notification of Personal Data Breach report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/gdpr-article-34-comm-data-breach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/gdpr-article-34-comm-data-breach/</guid><description>GDPR Article 34: Communication of a Personal Data Breach The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements outlined by GDPR.
The GDPR Article 34: Communication of a Personal Data Breach report describes and provides access to features in the Alert Logic consolethat help demonstrate compliance with GDPR Article 34.
To access the GDPR Article 34: Communication of a Personal Data Breach report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/gdpr-article-35-data-protection-impact-assessment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/gdpr-article-35-data-protection-impact-assessment/</guid><description>GDPR Article 35: Data Protection Impact Assessment The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements outlined by GDPR.
The GDPR Article 35: Data Protection Impact Assessment report describes and provides access to features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with GDPR Article 35.
To access the GDPR Article 35: Data Protection Impact Assessment report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.308-is-activity-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.308-is-activity-review/</guid><description>HIPAA 164.308(a)(1)(ii)(D)—Information System Activity Review The Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) Security Audit reports show available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the HIPAA Security Rule, as outlined in the HIPAA Audit Protocol.This report provides log review and log management incident information to help you demonstrate compliance with HIPAA 164.308(a)(1)(ii)(D).
To access the HIPAA 164.308(a)(1)(ii)(D) report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.308-login-monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.308-login-monitoring/</guid><description>HIPAA 164.308(a)(5)(ii)(C)—Login Monitoring The Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) Security Audit reports show available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the HIPAA Security Rule, as outlined in the HIPAA Audit Protocol.
This report provides login incidents for monitoring and review to help you demonstrate compliance with HIPAA 164.308(a)(5)(ii)(C).
To access the HIPAA 164.308(a)(5)(ii)(C) report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.308-protection-from-malicious-software/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.308-protection-from-malicious-software/</guid><description>HIPAA 164.308(a)(5)(ii)(B)—Protection from Malicious Software The Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) Security Audit reports show available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the HIPAA Security Rule, as outlined in the HIPAA Audit Protocol.
This report provides information on guarding against, detecting, and reporting malicious software to help you demonstrate compliance with HIPAA 164.308(a)(5)(ii)(B).
To access the HIPAA 164.312(a)(5)(ii)(B) report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.308-response-reporting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.308-response-reporting/</guid><description>HIPAA 164.308(a)(6)(ii)—Response and Reporting The Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) Security Audit reports show available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the HIPAA Security Rule, as outlined in the HIPAA Audit Protocol.
This report provides documentation of security incidents and notifications contacts to help you demonstrate compliance with HIPAA 164.308(a)(6)(ii).
To access the HIPAA 164.308(a)(6)(ii) report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.308-risk-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.308-risk-management/</guid><description>HIPAA 164.308(a)(1)(ii)(B)—Risk Management The Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) Security Audit reports show available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the HIPAA Security Rule, as outlined in the HIPAA Audit Protocol.
This report provides information on security measures that reduce risk and vulnerabilities to a reasonable and appropriate level to help you demonstrate compliance with HIPAA 164.308(a)(1)(ii)(B).
To access the HIPAA 164.308(a)(1)(ii)(B) report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.312-audit-controls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.312-audit-controls/</guid><description>HIPAA 164.312(b)—Audit Controls The Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) Security Audit reports show available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the HIPAA Security Rule, as outlined in the HIPAA Audit Protocol.
This report provides information on the implemented software or procedural mechanisms that record and examine activity in information systems to help you demonstrate compliance with HIPAA 164.312(b).
To access the HIPAA 164.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.312-integrity-controls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hipaa-164.312-integrity-controls/</guid><description>HIPAA 164.312(c)(1)—Integrity Controls The Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) Security Audit reports show available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the HIPAA Security Rule, as outlined in the HIPAA Audit Protocol.
This report provides guidance on how to use and access your File Integrity Monitoring (FIM) features to help you demonstrate compliance with HIPAA 164.312(c)(1).
To access the HIPAA 164.312(c)(1) report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hitrust-csf-01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hitrust-csf-01/</guid><description>HITRUST CSF 01.0 Access Control The HITRUST Common Security Framework (CSF) reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with HITRUST CSF control categories, as outlined in the HITRUST Risk Management Framework.
The HITRUST CSF 01.0 Access Control report describes how to use and access log searches and the list of users with access to security functions and access logs in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with Control Category 01.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hitrust-csf-03.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hitrust-csf-03.0/</guid><description>HITRUST CSF 03.0 Risk Management The HITRUST Common Security Framework (CSF) reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with HITRUST CSF control categories, as outlined in the HITRUST Risk Management Framework.
The HITRUST CSF 03.0 Risk Management report describes how to use and access vulnerability, threat risk index, and threat response reporting features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with Control Category 03.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hitrust-csf-06.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hitrust-csf-06.0/</guid><description>HITRUST CSF 06.0 Compliance The HITRUST Common Security Framework (CSF) reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with HITRUST CSF control categories, as outlined in the HITRUST Risk Management Framework.
The HITRUST CSF 06.0 Compliance report provides guidance on how to access configuration features in the Alert Logic console that help you demonstrate compliance with Control Category 6.0.
To access the HITRUST CSF 06.0 report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hitrust-csf-09.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hitrust-csf-09.0/</guid><description>HITRUST CSF 09.0 Communications and Operations Management The HITRUST Common Security Framework (CSF) reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with HITRUST CSF control categories, as outlined in the HITRUST Risk Management Framework.
The HITRUST CSF 09.0 Communication &amp;amp; Operations Management report provides guidance on how to access configuration features in the Alert Logic console to that help you demonstrate compliance with Control Category 09.0.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hitrust-csf-10.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hitrust-csf-10.0/</guid><description>HITRUST CSF 10.0 Information Systems Acquisition, Development, and Maintenance The HITRUST Common Security Framework (CSF) reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with HITRUST CSF control categories, as outlined in the HITRUST Risk Management Framework.
The HITRUST CSF 10.0 Information Systems Acquisition, Development, and Maintenance report describes how to access web application protection and vulnerability management features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with Control Category 10.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hitrust-csf-11.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/hitrust-csf-11.0/</guid><description>HITRUST CSF 11.0 Information Security Incident Management The HITRUST Common Security Framework (CSF) reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with HITRUST CSF control categories, as outlined in the HITRUST Risk Management Framework.
The HITRUST CSF 11.0 Information Security Incident Management report describes how to access security event and incident reporting features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with Control Category 11.0.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.1-access-control/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.1-access-control/</guid><description>NIST 800-171 3.1 - Access Control The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Special Publication 800-171 Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with the requirements outlined by NIST 800-171.
The NIST 800-171 3.1 - Access Control report provides links to log searches in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with NIST 800-171 3.1 Derived Security Requirements 3.1.7, 3.1.8, 3.1.11, and 3.1.12.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.11-risk-assessment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.11-risk-assessment/</guid><description>NIST 800-171 3.11 - Risk Assessment The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Special Publication 800-171 Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with the requirements outlined by NIST 800-171.
The NIST 800-171 3.11 - Risk Assessment report provides links to vulnerability scanning and vulnerability variance reporting features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with NIST 800-171 Derived Security Requirements 3.11.2 and 3.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.12-security-assessment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.12-security-assessment/</guid><description>NIST 800-171 3.12 - Security Assessment The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Special Publication 800-171 Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with the requirements outlined by NIST 800-171.
The NIST 800-171 3.12 - Security Assessment report provides links to vulnerability assessment and threat risk index reporting features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with NIST 800-171 Derived Security Requirement 3.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.13-system-and-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.13-system-and-communications/</guid><description>NIST 800-171 3.13 - System and Communications Protection The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Special Publication 800-171 Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with the requirements outlined by NIST 800-171.
The NIST 800-171 3.13 - System and Communications Protection report provides links to network IDS, vulnerability scan, and web application protection features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with NIST 800-171 Basic Security Requirement 3.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.14-system-and-information-integrity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.14-system-and-information-integrity/</guid><description>NIST 800-171 3.14 - System and Information Integrity The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Special Publication 800-171 Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with the requirements outlined by NIST 800-171.
The NIST 800-171 3.14 - System and Information Integrity report provides links to endpoint protection, web application protection, and log search features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with the following NIST 800-171 requirements:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.3-audit-and-accountability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.3-audit-and-accountability/</guid><description>NIST 800-171 3.3 - Audit and Accountability The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Special Publication 800-171 Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with the requirements outlined by NIST 800-171.
The NIST 800-171 3.3 - Audit and Accountability report provides links to log search, notifications, log review and event analysis reporting, file integrity monitoring, dashboards, and incident response features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with the following NIST 800-171 Basic Security and Derived Security Requirements:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.4-configuration-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.4-configuration-management/</guid><description>NIST 800-171 3.4 - Configuration Management The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Special Publication 800-171 Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with the requirements outlined by NIST 800-171.
The NIST 800-171 3.4 - Configuration Management report provides links to the exposures and endpoint protection features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with NIST 800-171 Derived security requirements 3.4.7 and 3.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.5-identification-and-authentication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.5-identification-and-authentication/</guid><description>NIST 800-171 3.5 - Identification and Authentication The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Special Publication 800-171 Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with the requirements outlined by NIST 800-171.
The NIST 800-171 3.5 - Identification and Authentication report provides links to log searches in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with NIST 800-171 Basic Security Requirement 3.5.2.
To access the NIST 800-171 3.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.6-incident-response/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/nist-800-171-3.6-incident-response/</guid><description>NIST 800-171 3.6 - Incident Response The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Special Publication 800-171 Audit reports provide documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with the requirements outlined by NIST 800-171.
The NIST 800-171 3.6 - Access Control report provides links to incident response and event analysis reporting features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with NIST 800-171 3.1 Basic Security Requirements 3.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.2.2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.2.2/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 10.2.2 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 10.2.2 report provides guidance for performing log searches that help you demonstrate compliance with Requirement 10.2.2.
To access the PCI Requirement 10.2.2 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.2.4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.2.4/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 10.2.4 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 10.2.4 report provides guidance for performing log searches that help you demonstrate compliance with Requirement 10.2.4.
To access the PCI Requirement 10.2.4 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.2.5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.2.5/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 10.2.5 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 10.2.5 report provides guidance for performing log searches that help you demonstrate compliance with Requirement 10.2.5.
To access the PCI Requirement 10.2.5 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.2.6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.2.6/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 10.2.6 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 10.2.6 report describes, and provides access to, log searches in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with Requirement 10.2.6.
To access the PCI Requirement 10.2.6 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.2.7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.2.7/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 10.2.7 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 10.2.7 report provides guidance for performing log searches that help you demonstrate compliance with Requirement 10.2.7.
To access the PCI Requirement 10.2.7 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.5.1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.5.1/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 10.5.1 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 10.5.1 report provides a list of the current log management users that help you demonstrate compliance with Requirement 10.5.1.
To access the PCI Requirement 10.5.1 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.5.5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.5.5/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 10.5.5 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 10.5.5 report provides guidance for how to access File Integrity Monitoring (FIM) features that help you demonstrate compliance with Requirement 10.5.5.
To access the PCI Requirement 10.5.5 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.6-incidents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.6-incidents/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 10.6 (Incidents) The PCI Requirement 10.6 (Incidents) report shows log review and log management incidents to help demonstrate compliance to Requirement 10.6 of PCI DSS.
This report is composed of three pages, Summary page, Log Review Incidents page, and the Log Management** Incidents** page. Click the Log Review Incidents icon () to see the Log Review Incidents page. Click the Log Management Incident icon () to see the Log Management Incidents page.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.6.1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.6.1/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 10.6.1 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 10.6.1 report provides Log Review incidents and Log Management incidents that help you demonstrate compliance with Requirement 10.6.1.
To access the PCI Requirement 10.6.1 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.7/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 10.7 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 10.7 report provides guidance for performing log searches that help you demonstrate compliance with Requirement 10.7.
To access the PCI Requirement 10.7 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-10.8/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 10.8 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 10.8 report provides guidance to demonstrate you have implemented a process for the timely detection and reporting failures of critical security control systems, in compliance with Requirement 10.8.
To access the PCI Requirement 10.8 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-11.2.1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-11.2.1/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 11.2.1 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 11.2.1 report provides guidance to demonstrate that quarterly internal vulnerability scans, &amp;ldquo;high-risk&amp;rdquo; vulnerabilities are rescanned, and performed by qualified personnel, in compliance with Requirement 11.2.1.
To access the PCI Requirement 11.2.1 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-11.2.2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-11.2.2/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 11.2.2 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 11.2.2 report provides guidance to demonstrate that quarterly external vulnerability scans and rescans are performed, in compliance with Requirement 11.2.2.
To access the PCI Requirement 11.2.2 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-11.4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-11.4/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 11.4 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 11.4 report shows Network IDS incidents and customer escalation contacts that help you demonstrate compliance with Requirement 11.4.
To access the PCI Requirement 11.4 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-11.4a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-11.4a/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 11.4 The PCI Requirement 11.4 report will soon be replaced by a newer version with the same name in the Alert Logic console. This document will also be replaced to reflect those changes. The new documentation that will replace this document can be found here.
The PCI Requirement 11.4 report shows Network IDS incidents and customer escalation contacts to help you demonstrate compliance to Requirement 11.4 of the PCI DSS.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-11.5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-11.5/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 11.5 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 11.5 report provides guidance on how to access File Integrity Monitoring (FIM) features that help you demonstrate compliance with Requirement 11.5.
To access the PCI Requirement 11.5 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-6.6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/pci-requirement-6.6/</guid><description>PCI Requirement 6.6 The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Audit reports provide available documentation and compliance artifacts that help you demonstrate compliance with requirements of the PCI DSS.
The PCI Requirement 6.6 report provides Alert Logic Managed Web Application Firewall (WAF) deployments, traffic, incidents, and attacks that help demonstrate compliance with Requirement 6.6.
To access the PCI Requirement 6.6 report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/reports/</guid><description>Compliance Reports The REPORTS page in the Alert Logic console provides access to data related to exposures and incidents Alert Logic found within your deployments. You can also view data related to your product usage within your accounts. For information on all the available report groups, see Reports Guide.
The Compliance report group provide convenient access to analysis, statistics, and trending data related to compliance assessment status and audit preparedness from your subscribed products and services.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-6.2-user-registration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-6.2-user-registration/</guid><description>SOC 2 Common Criteria 6.2 User Registration The SOC 2 Audit Reports provide documentation to help demonstrate compliance with the Trust Services Criteria established by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA). The SOC 2 CC6.2 User Registration report describes how to use and access log searches in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with Common Criteria (CC) 6.2.
To access the SOC 2 CC6.2 User Registration report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-6.3-access-modification-and-removal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-6.3-access-modification-and-removal/</guid><description>SOC 2 Common Criteria 6.3 Access Modification and Removal The SOC 2 Audit Reports provide documentation to help demonstrate compliance with the Trust Services Criteria established by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA). The SOC 2 CC6.3 Access Modification and Removal report describes how to use and access log searches, the list of users with access to security functions and access logs in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with Common Criteria (CC) 6.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-6.6-boundary-protection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-6.6-boundary-protection/</guid><description>SOC 2 Common Criteria 6.6 Boundary Protection The SOC 2 Audit Reports provide documentation to help demonstrate compliance with the Trust Services Criteria established by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA). The SOC 2 CC6.6 Boundary Protection report describes how to use and access threat detection, scanning, and web application protection features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with Common Criteria (CC) 6.6.
To access the SOC 2 CC6.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-6.8-unauthorized-and-malicious-code-protection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-6.8-unauthorized-and-malicious-code-protection/</guid><description>SOC 2 Common Criteria 6.8 Unauthorized and Malicious Code Protection The SOC 2 Audit Reports provide documentation to help demonstrate compliance with the Trust Services Criteria established by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA). The SOC 2 CC6.8 Unauthorized and Malicious Code Protection report describes how to access File Integrity Monitoring (FIM) and endpoint protection features in the Alert Logic console to that help you demonstrate compliance with Common Criteria (CC) 6.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-7.1-configuration-and-vulnerability-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-7.1-configuration-and-vulnerability-management/</guid><description>SOC 2 Common Criteria 7.1 Configuration and Vulnerability Management The SOC 2 Audit Reports provide documentation to help demonstrate compliance with the Trust Services Criteria established by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA). The SOC 2 CC7.1 Configuration and Vulnerability Management report describes how to access File Integrity Monitoring (FIM), scan scheduling, and vulnerability reporting features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with Common Criteria (CC) 7.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-7.2-security-event-anomaly-detection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-7.2-security-event-anomaly-detection/</guid><description>SOC 2 Common Criteria 7.2 Security Event and Anomaly Detection The SOC 2 Audit Reports provide documentation to help demonstrate compliance with the Trust Services Criteria established by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA). The SOC 2 CC7.2 Security Event and Anomaly Detection report describes how to access security event and threat response reporting features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with Common Criteria (CC) 7.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-7.3-incident-detection-reponse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-7.3-incident-detection-reponse/</guid><description>SOC 2 Common Criteria 7.3 Incident Detection and Response The SOC 2 Audit Reports provide documentation to help demonstrate compliance with the Trust Services Criteria established by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA). The SOC 2 CC7.3 Incident Detection and Response report describes how to access security event and threat response reporting features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with Common Criteria (CC) 7.3.
To access the SOC 2 CC7.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-7.4-incident-containment-remediation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2-cc-7.4-incident-containment-remediation/</guid><description>SOC 2 Common Criteria 7.4 Incident Containment and Remediation The SOC 2 Audit Reports provide documentation to help demonstrate compliance with the Trust Services Criteria established by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA). The SOC 2 CC7.4 Incident Containment and Remediation report describes how to access vulnerability and threat response reporting features in the Alert Logic console that help demonstrate compliance with Common Criteria (CC) 7.4
To access the SOC 2 CC7.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/compliance/soc2/</guid><description>SOC 2 Audit Reports This documentation is intended for customers previewing information for the new SOC 2 Audit reports. To learn about existing reports available to you in the Alert Logic console, go to the Reports Guide.
The SOC 2 Audit Reports provides documentation to help demonstrate compliance with the Trust Services Criteria controls established by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA).
You will have access to run following reports that demonstrate compliance with specific common criteria of SOC 2:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/download-option/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/download-option/</guid><description>Report Download Option Alert Logic allows you to download report information in the following formats:
Image Data Crosstab PDF PowerPoint You can download all the contents from a report, download specified sections from a report, or download specified sections from any reports in the same report group to organize and combine information to best meet your needs. This feature can be useful when gathering information to meet compliance requirements or you need to share certain information with other people from your organization.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/remediations/configuration-remediation-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/remediations/configuration-remediation-trends/</guid><description>Configuration Remediation Trends Report The Configuration Remediation Trends report evaluates the overall responsiveness of your organization to known issues in the Remediations page that degrade the effectiveness of collection, scanning, detection, or response capabilities deployed in your environment.
To access the Configuration Remediation Trends report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Remediations. Under Configuration Remediations, click VIEW. Click Configuration Remediation Trends.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/remediations/reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/remediations/reports/</guid><description>Remediations Reports The REPORTS page in the Alert Logic console provides access to data related to exposures and incidents Alert Logic found within your deployments. You can also view data related to your product usage within your accounts. For information on all the available report groups, see Reports Guide.
The Remediations reports group provide convenient access to analysis, statistics, assessments, and trending data related to configuration issues and security exposures from your subscribed products and services.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/remediations/security-remediation-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/remediations/security-remediation-trends/</guid><description>Security Remediation Trends The Security Remediation Trends report evaluates the overall responsiveness to known issues in the Remediations page that expose your assets to threats.
To access the Security Remediation Trend:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Remediations. Under Security Remediations, click VIEW. Click Security Remediation Trends. Filter the report To refine your findings, you can filter your report by Date Range, Customer Account, Deployment Name, Network, and Asset Tags.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/reports/</guid><description>Reports Guide The Reports page in the Alert Logic console provides access to data related to exposures and incidents Alert Logic found within your deployments. You can also view data related to your product usage within your accounts.
Report data is cached and refreshed at regular intervals. As a result, periodic delays to reflect the latest data in the console can occur.
Depending on your Alert Logic subscriptions, you will see some or all of the following report types:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/enterprise-risk/monthly-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/enterprise-risk/monthly-enterprise/</guid><description>Monthly Enterprise Risk The Monthly Enterprise Risk report provides valuable insights and analysis of your incidents, events, and vulnerabilities in your environment. Use this report to evaluate threats and incidents, and your response efforts, validate events and focus your efforts, and gain insights into the effectiveness of your vulnerability management.
This report presents data for an entire month, which immediately becomes available in the beginning of the following month.
To access the Monthly Enterprise report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/enterprise-risk/weekly-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/enterprise-risk/weekly-enterprise/</guid><description>Weekly Enterprise Risk The Weekly Enterprise Risk report provides valuable insights and analysis of your incidents, events, and vulnerabilities in your environment. Use this report to evaluate threats and incidents, and your response efforts, validate events and focus your efforts, and gain insights into the effectiveness of your vulnerability management.
This report presents data for an entire week, from Monday through Sunday, which immediately becomes available in the beginning of the following week.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/monthly-security-posture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/monthly-security-posture/</guid><description>Monthly Security Posture Report The Monthly Security Posture report provides the current and historic monthly security risk and health posture of your environment, including configuration and security remediations, risk posture overviews, vulnerabilities assessments, and threat analysis.
Use this report to prioritize opportunities to improve your overall security posture and optimize security collection, detection, and response capabilities deployed in your environment.
This report is composed of the following six pages:
Summary Configuration Remediations Risk Index Vulnerabilities Security Remediations Threats To page through the report, go to the next page, click the arrow icon () on the top right of the report.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/reports/</guid><description>Risk Reports The REPORTS page in the Alert Logic console provides access to data related to exposures and incidents Alert Logic found within your deployments. You can also view data related to your product usage within your accounts. For information on all the available report groups, see Reports Guide.
The Risk reports group provide convenient access to analysis, statistics, assessments, and trending data related to your security and health posture and threat risk index.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/top-ten-tri-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/top-ten-tri-list/</guid><description>Top 10 TRI Lists The Top 10 TRI Lists report provides top 10 lists of your most vulnerable hosts by TRI score, and the top 10 vulnerabilities by TRI Score.
Use this report to enable a proactive risk management approach and prioritize risk mitigation efforts on specific areas in your environment.
To access the Top 10 TRI Lists report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/tri-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/tri-summary/</guid><description>TRI Summary The TRI Summary report provides a summary of the recent threat risk index (TRI) scores of your environment, including the overall TRI score and trends, score details, and risk index asset distribution charts.
Use this report to enable a proactive risk management approach and prioritize risk mitigation efforts on specific areas in your environment.
To access the TRI Summary report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/tri-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/risk/tri-trends/</guid><description>TRI Trends Report The TRI Trends report provides insights into threat risk index (TRI) scores and trends in reducing risks, including average TRI scores, total vulnerability and host counts, internet-facing vulnerabilities, exploit availability, and last scanned age.
Use this report to identify patterns in the overall TRI score trends and contributing factors, gauge progress made, and focus efforts on key areas to reduce threats in your environment.
To access the TRI Summary report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/capability-usage/log-collection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/capability-usage/log-collection/</guid><description>Log Collection The Log Collection report provides visibility into log collection volume and log messages processed in your environment, including log collection per day and a list of collectors with volume by GB, EPS or log messages. Use this report to support log collection configuration and optimization efforts in your environment.
To access the Log Collection report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/capability-usage/network-ids-traffic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/capability-usage/network-ids-traffic/</guid><description>IDS Traffic This report provides visibility into IDS traffic volume and collections processed in your environment, including IDS traffic per day, a list of collectors with traffic packets and megabytes, and a top ten collector list. Use this report to support IDS configuration and optimization efforts in your environment.
To access the Network IDS Traffic report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Service.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/capability-usage/top-10-ids-assets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/capability-usage/top-10-ids-assets/</guid><description>Top 10 IDS Assets This report provides visibility into the top 10 sources of IDS traffic volume processed in your environment, listed by megabytes and packets. Use this report to support IDS configuration and optimization efforts in your environment.
To access the Top 10 IDS Assets Traffic report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Service. Under Capability Usage, click VIEW.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/capability-usage/top-ten-log-collectors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/capability-usage/top-ten-log-collectors/</guid><description>Top 10 Log Collectors The Top 10 Log Collectors report provides visibility into the log collector volume with top ten collector lists measured by GBs, EPs, or log messages. Use this report to support log collection configuration and optimization efforts in your environment.
To access the Top 10 Log Collectors report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Service.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/capability-usage/waf-traffic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/capability-usage/waf-traffic/</guid><description>WAF Traffic The WAF Traffic report provides visibility into WAF traffic volume and requests processed in your environment, including WAF traffic per day measured by request or data size (in MB), and an appliance list with traffic requests and data size. Use this report to support WAF configuration and optimization efforts in your environment.
To access the WAF Traffic report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/entitlement/entitlement-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/entitlement/entitlement-summary/</guid><description>Entitlement Summary The Entitlement Summary report provides a daily summary of your entitlement and usage, including count and percentage of nodes used, nodes remaining, and list of deployments with the protected node counts.
Use this report to confirm entitlement node counts are consistent with what you purchased, determine subscription levels of protection are correct, and make adjustments to optimize usage and predict costs.
To access the Entitlement Summary report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/entitlement/entitlement-usage-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/entitlement/entitlement-usage-trends/</guid><description>Entitlement Usage Trends The Entitlement Usage Trends report provides a summary of your entitlement usage, including nodes used trends and entitlement change trends.
Use this report to confirm entitlement node count changes are consistent with what you purchased, determine subscription levels of protection are aligned with changes in your environment, and identify patterns to keep cost predictable.
To access the Entitlement Usage Trends report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/entitlement/lm-pro-entitlement-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/entitlement/lm-pro-entitlement-summary/</guid><description>LM Professional Entitlement Summary The LM Professional Entitlement Summary report provides a daily summary of your LM Professional entitlement and usage, including count of nodes used, nodes remaining, usage for your deployments, and trends of nodes used and entitlement changes.
Use this report to confirm entitlement node counts are consistent with what you purchased, make adjustments to optimize usage, and predict costs.
To access the LM Professional Entitlement Summary report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/entitlement/tm-pro-entitlement-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/entitlement/tm-pro-entitlement-summary/</guid><description>TM Professional Entitlement Summary The TM Professional Entitlement Summary report provides a daily summary of your TM Professional entitlement and usage, including count of nodes used, nodes remaining, usage for your deployments, and trends of nodes used and entitlement changes.
Use this report to confirm entitlement node counts are consistent with what you purchased, make adjustments to optimize usage, and predict costs.
To access the TM Professional Entitlement Summary report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/collection-issues-digest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/collection-issues-digest/</guid><description>Collection Issues Digest The Collection Issues Digest report provides insight into the daily issues related to log data collection and Network IDS traffic, including a comparison of health statuses, top five lists, and a list of open remediations to fix configuration issues. Use this report to fix collection issues and support optimization efforts in your environment.
To access the Collection Issues Digest report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/current-ssl-certificates-status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/current-ssl-certificates-status/</guid><description>SSL Certification Expiration Status The SSL Certification Expiration Status report provides insights into the statuses of SSL keys and certificates that are used on Alert Logic appliances to decrypt network traffic. Use this report to be aware of approaching expiration dates of SSL keys and certificates, and then take appropriate actions to avoid expired certificates and degraded performance.
For information about managing SSL keys and certificates, see Certificates and Keys.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/daily-health-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/daily-health-summary/</guid><description>Daily Health Summary The Daily Health Summary report provides insight into the daily issues in your environment related to your protected network health status, data collection and network IDS traffic, and hosts missing agents. This report is composed of three sections: Network Health Status, Collection Issues, and Missing Agent. Use this report to improve network protection, fix configuration issues, and support optimization efforts in your environment.
To access the Daily Health Summary report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/missing-agent-digest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/missing-agent-digest/</guid><description>Missing Agent Digest The Missing Agent Digest report provides insight into the daily issues related to hosts that are missing agents, including a comparison of missing agent statuses, top ten lists, and a list of hosts with missing agents.
To access Missing Agent Digest report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Service. Under Health, click VIEW. Click Missing Agent Digest.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/monthly-health-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/monthly-health-summary/</guid><description>Monthly Health Summary The Monthly Health Summary report provides insight into the monthly issues in your environment related to your protected network health status, data collection and network IDS traffic, and hosts missing agents. This report is composed of three sections: Network Health Status, Collection Issues, and Missing Agent. Use this report to improve network protection, fix configuration issues, and support optimization efforts in your environment.
To access the Monthly Health Summary report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/network-health-digest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/network-health-digest/</guid><description>Network Health Status Digest The Network Health Status Digest report provides insight into the daily issues related to protected networks in your environment, including a comparison of health statuses, top ten lists, and total number of open remediations for each network. Use this report to improve network protection, fix configuration issues, and support optimization efforts in your environment.
To access the Network Health Digest report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/weekly-health-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/health/weekly-health-summary/</guid><description>Weekly Health Summary The Weekly Health Summary report provides insight into the weekly issues in your environment related to your protected network health status, data collection and network IDS traffic, and hosts missing agents. This report is composed of three sections: Network Health Status, Collection Issues, and Missing Agent. Use this report to improve network protection, fix configuration issues, and support optimization efforts in your environment.
To access the Weekly Health Summary report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/reports/</guid><description>Service Reports The REPORTS page in the Alert Logic console provides access to data related to exposures and incidents Alert Logic found within your deployments. You can also view data related to your product usage within your accounts. For information on all the available report groups, see Reports Guide.
The Service reports provide convenient access to data related to entitlements, capability usage, users and security content for your subscribed products and services.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/users/current-users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/users/current-users/</guid><description>Current Users The Current Users report provides a visual overview of the users in your customer account by active or inactive status, user role, or multi-factor authentication settings. The report also provides a list of account details for each user.
Use this report to help manage user accounts for your organization. The Current Users report allows you to evaluate user settings to:
Ensure user accounts that no longer require access to the Alert Logic console are either inactive or deleted Determine the roles assigned to each user account Determine whether multi-factor authentication (MFA) is enabled for user accounts To access the Current Users report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/users/login-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/users/login-trends/</guid><description>User Login Trends The User Login Trends report provides a visual overview and a detailed list of the users who log into the Alert Logic console, how often and when.
Use this report to identify patterns in user logins within your account.
To access the User Login Trends report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Service. Under Users, click VIEW.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/users/subscribed-notification-users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/service/users/subscribed-notification-users/</guid><description>Subscribed Notification Users The Subscribed Notification Users report provides a list of users subscribed to receive notifications for specified customer accounts. These are users set up to receive automated email notifications from the Notifications page.
To access the Subscribed Notification Users report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Service. Under Users, click VIEW. Click Subscribed Notification Users. Filter the report To refine your findings, you can filter your report by Customer Account.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/aws-incident-analysis/aws-incident-daily-digest-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/aws-incident-analysis/aws-incident-daily-digest-trends/</guid><description>AWS Incident Daily Digest Trends The AWS Incident Daily Digest Trends report provides a histogram chart that allows you to review trends in daily Amazon Web Services (AWS) incidents for a selected date range. Use this report to evaluate trends in AWS incidents by threat level, classification, and type.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
You must configure Amazon GuardDuty for associated incidents to be d[AWS Incident Daily Digest Trends](#)isplayed in Alert Logic console.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/aws-incident-analysis/aws-incident-daily-digest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/aws-incident-analysis/aws-incident-daily-digest/</guid><description>AWS Incident Daily Digest Report The AWS Incident Daily Digest report displays Amazon GuardDuty and Network IDS incidents detected on the previous day for the selected Amazon Web Services (AWS) deployments and containers. Use this report to evaluate daily AWS incidents by threat level, classification, and type.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
You must configure Amazon GuardDuty for associated incidents to be displayed in Alert Logic console. For more information, see [Integrate Amazon GuardDuty Findings into Alert Logic Incidents](.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/aws-incident-analysis/aws-incident-dist-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/aws-incident-analysis/aws-incident-dist-explorer/</guid><description>AWS Incident Distribution Explorer The AWS Incident Distribution Explorer report presents incident trends by threat level, classification, and type for the selected date range. The report presents the information in pie graphs and a series of histograms in each category for the selected date range.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
You must configure Amazon GuardDuty for associated incidents to be displayed in Alert Logic console. For more information, see [Integrate Amazon GuardDuty Findings into Alert Logic Incidents](.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/aws-incident-analysis/aws-targeted-deployment-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/aws-incident-analysis/aws-targeted-deployment-explorer/</guid><description>AWS Targeted Deployment Explorer The AWS Targeted Deployment Explorer report displays the Amazon GuardDutyand Network IDS incident distribution by a selected AWS account ID, region, VPC, container image name, Security Group, or subnet target type.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
You must integrate Amazon GuardDuty for associated incidents to be displayed in Alert Logic console. For more information, see [Integrate Amazon GuardDuty Findings into Alert Logic Incidents](../../../../configure/integrate-guard-duty-findings.md). To access the AWS Targeted Deployment Explorer report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/aws-incident-analysis/aws-targeted-deployment-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/aws-incident-analysis/aws-targeted-deployment-trends/</guid><description>AWS Targeted Deployment Trends The AWS Targeted Deployment Trends report provides a bar and histogram chart that allows you to review trends in Amazon GuardDuty and Network IDS incidents for a date range by Amazon Web Services (AWS) account ID, region, VPC, container image, subnet and Security Group.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
You must integrate Amazon GuardDuty for associated incidents to be displayed in Alert Logic console. For more information, see [Integrate Amazon GuardDuty Findings into Alert Logic Incidents](.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/azure-incident-analysis/azure-incident-daily-digest-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/azure-incident-analysis/azure-incident-daily-digest-trends/</guid><description>Azure Incident Daily Digest Trends Report The Azure Incident Daily Digest Trends report provides a histogram chart that allows you to review daily trends in Azure incidents for a selected date range. Use this report to evaluate trends in Azure incidents by threat level, classification, and type.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Azure Incident Daily Digest Trends report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/azure-incident-analysis/azure-incident-daily-digest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/azure-incident-analysis/azure-incident-daily-digest/</guid><description>Azure Incident Daily Digest Report The Azure Incident Daily Digest report displays Network IDS incidents detected on the previous day for the selected Azure deployments and containers. Use this report to evaluate daily Azure incidents by threat level, classification, or by incident type.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Azure Incident Daily Digest report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/azure-incident-analysis/azure-incident-dist-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/azure-incident-analysis/azure-incident-dist-explorer/</guid><description>Azure Incident Distribution Explorer Report The Azure Incident Distribution Explorer report presents incident trends by threat level, classification, and type for the selected date range. The report presents the information in pie graphs and a series of histograms in each category for the selected date range.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Azure Incident Distribution Explorer report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/azure-incident-analysis/azure-targeted-deployment-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/azure-incident-analysis/azure-targeted-deployment-explorer/</guid><description>Azure Targeted Deployment Explorer The Azure Targeted Deployment Explorer report displays the Network IDS incident distribution by a selected native account ID, region, VNet, container image name, Security Group, or subnet target type.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Azure Targeted Deployment Explorer report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Threats. Under Azure Incident Analysis, click VIEW.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/azure-incident-analysis/azure-targeted-deployment-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/azure-incident-analysis/azure-targeted-deployment-trends/</guid><description>Azure Targeted Deployment Trends The Azure Targeted Deployment Trends report provides a bar and histogram chart that allows you to review trends in Network IDS incidents for a date range by native account ID, region, VNet, container image, subnet and security group.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Azure Targeted Deployment Trends Report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/event-analysis/monthly-event-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/event-analysis/monthly-event-analysis/</guid><description>Monthly Event Analysis The Monthly Event Analysis provides visibility into Network IDS events processed in your environment, including event classification, top signatures, and events per day for the selected month. Use this report to validate your IDS events and focus efforts on sources that were detected and processed in your environment.
This report presents data for an entire month, which immediately becomes available in the beginning of the following month.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/event-analysis/network-ids-events-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/event-analysis/network-ids-events-explorer/</guid><description>Network IDS Events Explorer The Network IDS Event Explorer report provides visibility into Network IDS events processed in your environment, including events per day, visualizations by payload and classification, and top signatures.
Use this report to validate your IDS events and focus efforts on sources that were detected and processed in your environment.
To access the Network IDS Event Explorer report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/event-analysis/top-sources-destinations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/event-analysis/top-sources-destinations/</guid><description>Top Event Sources and Destinations The Top Event Sources and Destinations report lists the top source and destination IP addresses and ports for IDS events in your environment. Use this report to validate your IDS events and focus efforts.
To access the Top Event Sources and Destinations report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Threats. Under Event Analysis, click VIEW.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/event-analysis/weekly-event-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/event-analysis/weekly-event-analysis/</guid><description>Weekly Event Analysis The Weekly Event Analysis provides visibility into Network IDS events processed in your environment, including event classification, top signatures, and events per day for the selected week. Use this report to validate your IDS events and focus efforts on sources that were detected and processed in your environment.
This report presents data for an entire week, from Monday through Sunday, which immediately becomes available in the beginning of the following week.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-account-summary/monthly-incident-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-account-summary/monthly-incident-account/</guid><description>Monthly Incident Account Summary The Monthly Incident Summary report provides the current distribution and trending data for incidents detected across your customer accounts or deployments. Use the report to evaluate accounts or deployments by top incident count, threat level, count by week and threat level, detection source, escalation status, type, sub-type, top attackers, and top targets.
To access the Monthly Incident Account Summary report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-account-summary/weekly-incident-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-account-summary/weekly-incident-account/</guid><description>Weekly Incident Account Summary The Weekly Incident Summary report provides the current distribution and trending data for incidents detected across your customer accounts or deployments. Use the report to evaluate accounts or deployments by top incident count, threat level, count by week and threat level, detection source, escalation status, type, sub-type, top attackers, and top targets.
To access the Weekly Incident Account Summary report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/beta-incident-daily-digest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/beta-incident-daily-digest/</guid><description>Incident Daily Digest The Incident Daily Digest report provides the incidents detected on the previous day for the selected detection types. Use this report to evaluate daily incidents by threat level, classification, top attackers, and top targets.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Incident Daily Digest report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Threats.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-attacker-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-attacker-explorer/</guid><description>Incident Attacker Explorer The Incident Attacker Explorer provides visibility into the top 10 attackers and geolocations, with visualizations and lists of incidents by threat level, classification, and incident type. Use this report to review attacks on your environment.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Incident Attacker Explorer report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Threats.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-daily-digest-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-daily-digest-1/</guid><description>Incident Daily Digest The Incident Daily Digest report provides the incidents detected on the previous day for the selected detection types. Use this report to evaluate daily incidents by threat level, classification, and type.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Incident Daily Digest report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Threats. Under Incident Analysis, click VIEW.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-daily-digest-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-daily-digest-trends/</guid><description>Incident Daily Digest Trends The Incident Daily Digest Trends report provides a histogram chart that allows you to review trends in the daily incident digest results for a selected date range. Use this report to evaluate trends in daily incident digest results by threat level, classification, and type.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Incident Daily Digest Trends report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-daily-digest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-daily-digest/</guid><description>Incident Daily Digest The Incident Daily Digest report provides the incidents detected on the previous day for the selected detection types. Use this report to evaluate daily incidents by threat level, classification, top attackers, and top targets.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Incident Daily Digest report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Threats.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-dist-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-dist-explorer/</guid><description>Incident Distribution Explorer The Incident Distribution Explorer report presents incident trends by detection source, status, threat level, classification, type, and sub-type for the selected date range. The report presents the information in pie graphs and a series of histograms in each category for the selected date range.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Incident Distribution Explorer report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-target-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-target-explorer/</guid><description>Incident Target Explorer Report The Incident Target Explorer provides visibility into the most targeted IP addresses with visualizations and lists of incidents by threat level, classification, and incident type. Use this report to evaluate threats and incidents in your environment, and learn about emerging threats.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Incident Target Explorer:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-workflow-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/incident-workflow-explorer/</guid><description>Incident Workflow Explorer Report The Incident Workflow Explorer report tracks and evaluates daily workflow actions performed in the Incidents console to determine how often incidents are suppressed from reports, the Incident summary page, and the Security Posture page.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
To access the Incident Workflow Explorer:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Threats.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/monthly-incident/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/monthly-incident/</guid><description>Monthly Incident Analysis The Monthly Incident Analysis report provides visibility into threats and incidents in your environment, including incident statuses, threat levels, classification, daily incident count, and top ten lists. Use this report to evaluate threats and incidents, and your response efforts, and learn about emerging threats.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
This report presents data for an entire month, which immediately becomes available in the beginning of the following month.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/weekly-incident/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/incident-analysis/weekly-incident/</guid><description>Weekly Incident Analysis The Weekly Incident Analysis report provides visibility into threats and incidents in your environment, including incident statuses, threat levels, classification, daily incident count, and top ten lists. Use this report to evaluate threats and incidents, and your response efforts, and learn about emerging threats.
For more information about incidents, see Incidents.
This report presents data for an entire week, from Monday through Sunday, which immediately becomes available in the beginning of the following week.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/log-anomaly-analysis/daily-log-anomaly-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/log-anomaly-analysis/daily-log-anomaly-analysis/</guid><description>Daily Log Anomaly Analysis The Daily Log Anomaly Analysis report provides valuable insights into the daily log anomalies from all monitored log sources, and notes from Alert Logic analysts. The Daily Log Anomaly Analysis report compares the anomaly trend between the selected day and the previous day. Use this report to address and further analyze customer, host, and user anomalies, and administrator activities found in your environment.
To access the Daily Log Anomaly Analysis report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/log-anomaly-analysis/monthly-log-anomaly-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/log-anomaly-analysis/monthly-log-anomaly-analysis/</guid><description>Monthly Log Anomaly Analysis The Monthly Log Anomaly Analysis report provides valuable insights into the monthly log anomalies from all monitored log sources, and notes from Alert Logic analysts. The Monthly Log Anomaly Analysis report compares the anomaly trend between the selected month and the previous month. Use this report to address and further analyze customer, host, and user anomalies, and administrator activities found in your environment.
To access the Monthly Log Anomaly Analysis report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/log-review-analysis/monthly-log-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/log-review-analysis/monthly-log-review/</guid><description>Monthly Log Review Report The Monthly Log Review report provides a monthly summary analysis of your Log Review incidents, including count and percentage of total incidents of each status, a daily histogram chart, and a comparison to the previous month.
This report is composed of the Monthly Log Review page and the Log Review Comparison page. To see the Log Review Comparison page, click the arrow icon () on the top right of the report.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/observational-analysis/daily-log-anomalies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/observational-analysis/daily-log-anomalies/</guid><description>Daily Log Anomaly Analysis The Daily Log Anomaly Analysis report provides valuable insights into the daily log anomalies from all monitored log sources, and notes from Alert Logic analysts. The Daily Log Anomaly Analysis report compares the anomaly trend between the selected day and the previous day. Use this report to address and further analyze customer, host, and user anomalies, and administrator activities found in your environment.
To access the Daily Log Anomaly Analysis report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/observational-analysis/monthly-log-anomalies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/observational-analysis/monthly-log-anomalies/</guid><description>Monthly Log Anomaly Analysis The Monthly Log Anomaly Analysis report provides valuable insights into the monthly log anomalies from all monitored log sources, and notes from Alert Logic analysts. The Monthly Log Anomaly Analysis report compares the anomaly trend between the selected day and the previous day. Use this report to address and further analyze customer, host, and user anomalies, and administrator activities found in your environment.
To access the Monthly Log Anomaly Analysis report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/reports/</guid><description>Threats Reports The REPORTS tab in the Alert Logic console provides access to data related to exposures and incidents Alert Logic found within your deployments. You can also view data related to your product usage within your accounts. For information on all the available report groups, see Reports Guide.
The Threats reports provide convenient access to analysis, statistics, assessments, and trending data related to threats and incidents detected from your subscribed products and services.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/web-application-analysis/waf-violation-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/web-application-analysis/waf-violation-explorer/</guid><description>WAF Violation Explorer Report The WAF Violation Explorer report provides visibility into blocked Alert Logic Managed Web Application Firewall (WAF) requests and attempted web application attacks, including total and blocked WAF policy violations counts, violations by day, operating mode, risk level, attack class, and type.
Use this report to validate your WAF policies and focus efforts on tuning your configurations.
To access the WAF Violation Explorer report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/web-application-analysis/waf-violation-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/threats/web-application-analysis/waf-violation-trends/</guid><description>WAF Violation Trends The WAF Violation Trends report provides insights into patterns in your Alert Logic Managed Web Application Firewall (WAF) violations, including violation distribution and trends categorized by action, risk level, attack class, violation type, response code, method, and protocol.
To access the WAF Violation Trends report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Threats. Under Web Application Analysis, click VIEW.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/current-vulnerabilities-breakdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/current-vulnerabilities-breakdown/</guid><description>Current Vulnerabilities Breakdown Current Vulnerabilities Breakdown report provides a breakdown of current vulnerable hosts and vulnerability instances ranked by count severity with vulnerability detail. Use this report to gain insights into the effectiveness of your vulnerability management, help prioritize your efforts, and focus on specific areas in your environment.
To access the Current Vulnerabilities Breakdown report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/current-vulnerability-finder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/current-vulnerability-finder/</guid><description>Current Vulnerability Finder Report The Current Vulnerability Finder report provides insights into current vulnerabilities found in your environment matching specific criteria and the detailed breakdown of vulnerability instances on impacted assets.
Use this report to address and further analyze specific vulnerabilities and vulnerability instances found in your environment. You must filter and enter information in 3 steps to narrow down results specific to match the vulnerabilities you are searching. When you find data specific to match your needs, you can view and export reports in CSV or PDF format.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/current-vulnerable-hosts-breakdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/current-vulnerable-hosts-breakdown/</guid><description>Current Vulnerable Hosts Breakdown Current Vulnerable Hosts Breakdown report provides a breakdown of current vulnerable hosts and vulnerability instances ranked by count severity with asset-level detail. Use this report to gain insights into the effectiveness of your vulnerability management, help prioritize your efforts, and focus on specific areas in your environment.
To access the Current Vulnerable Hosts Breakdown report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/daily-vulnerability-variance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/daily-vulnerability-variance/</guid><description>Daily Vulnerability Variance The Daily Vulnerability Variance report provides a comparison of total unresolved, new, and resolved vulnerability instances in your environment from the previous day. Use this report to gain insights into the effectiveness of your vulnerability management and remediation efforts.
To access the Daily Vulnerability Variance report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Vulnerabilities. Under Vulnerability Variance, click VIEW.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/last-scanned-breakdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/last-scanned-breakdown/</guid><description>Last Scanned Breakdown Last Scanned Breakdown report provides visibility on when your assets were last scanned for vulnerabilities. Use this report to know which assets must be scanned immediately, gain insights into your last scans, help optimize your scan schedule configuration, and focus on specific areas in your environment.
To access the Last Scanned Breakdown report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/monthly-vulnerability-variance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/monthly-vulnerability-variance/</guid><description>Monthly Vulnerability Variance The Monthly Vulnerability Variance report provides a comparison of total unresolved, new, and resolved vulnerability instances in your environment from the previous month. Use this report to gain insights into the effectiveness of your vulnerability management and remediation efforts.
To access the Monthly Vulnerability Variance report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Vulnerabilities. Under Vulnerability Variance, click VIEW.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/reports/</guid><description>Vulnerabilities Reports The REPORTS tab in the Alert Logic console provides access to data related to exposures and incidents Alert Logic found within your deployments. You can also view data related to your product usage within your accounts. For information on all the available report groups, see Reports Guide.
The Vulnerability Reports provide convenient access to analysis, statistics, assessments, and trending data related to vulnerabilities discovered in your environment based on scanning outcomes.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/scan-schedule-breakdown/scan-details-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/scan-schedule-breakdown/scan-details-list/</guid><description>Scan Details List The Scan Details List report provides a detailed list of each vulnerability found by the selected scan with information on vulnerability name, CVSS score, severity, affected assets, host name, IP address, protocol, port, first seen, and last scanned. Use this report to investigate vulnerabilities detected in specific scans.
To access the Scan Details List report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/scan-schedule-breakdown/scan-host-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/scan-schedule-breakdown/scan-host-summary/</guid><description>Scan Host Summary The Scan Host Summary report provides a breakdown of vulnerable hosts and vulnerability instances found by the selected scan with asset-level detail. Use this report to help prioritize remediation efforts.
To access the Scan Host Summary report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Vulnerabilities. Under Scan Schedule Breakdown, click VIEW. Click Scan Host Summary. View the report To view the report, you must select a single value for Customer Account, Deployment Name, Scan Schedule Name, and Scan Start Date.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/scan-schedule-breakdown/scan-variance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/scan-schedule-breakdown/scan-variance/</guid><description>Scan Variance The Scan Variance report provides a comparison of new, resolved, and unresolved vulnerability instances found by the selected scan. Use this report to gain insights into the effectiveness of your vulnerability management and remediation efforts.
To access the Scan Variance report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Vulnerabilities. Under Scan Schedule Breakdown, click VIEW. Click Scan Variance.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/monthly-vulnerability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/monthly-vulnerability/</guid><description>Monthly Vulnerability Analysis The Monthly Vulnerability Analysis report provides insights into vulnerabilities and vulnerable assets found in your environment, including vulnerabilities by severity and age, vulnerability trends, vulnerabilities by day and severity, and top vulnerable hosts, networks, and deployment lists for the selected month. Use this report to gain insights into the effectiveness of your vulnerability management, help prioritize your efforts, and focus on specific areas in your environment.
This report presents data for an entire month, which immediately becomes available in the beginning of the following month.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerability-change-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerability-change-trends/</guid><description>Monthly Vulnerability Change Trends The Monthly Vulnerability Change Trends report provides a summary of the percentage and count changes of vulnerabilities, and trend by total and severity.
Alert Logic assigns each vulnerability one of the following severities with corresponding icon based on the CVSS v2 score set by the National Institute of Standards and Technology, and reported to the National Vulnerability Database:
Severity CVSS base score High 7.0 - 10.0 Medium 4.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerability-distribution-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerability-distribution-explorer/</guid><description>Monthly Vulnerability Distribution Explorer The Monthly Vulnerability Distribution Explorer report provides insights into patterns from the vulnerabilities found in your environment, including vulnerability distribution and trends categorized by status, exploitability, severity, age, operating system, and asset type. Use this report to help you optimize your vulnerability management process.
To access the Monthly Vulnerability Distribution Explorer report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerability-host-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerability-host-explorer/</guid><description>Monthly Vulnerable Hosts Explorer The Monthly Vulnerability Hosts Explorer report provides a summary of the most vulnerable assets in your environment. The report provides the following:
Total hosts count and vulnerable hosts count Percentages of hosts with vulnerabilities Host distributions by CVSS severity ratings The top 10 view of your most vulnerable hosts Alert Logic assigns each vulnerability one of the following severities with corresponding icon based on the CVSS v2 score set by the National Institute of Standards and Technology, and reported to the National Vulnerability Database:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerability-lists/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerability-lists/</guid><description>List of Vulnerabilities The List of Vulnerabilities report returns a tabular list of all current vulnerabilities, details about each vulnerability, and information about the assets affected by the vulnerability. Use this report to address and further analyze specific vulnerabilities and vulnerability instances found in your environment.
To access the List of Vulnerabilities report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerability-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerability-summary/</guid><description>Monthly Vulnerability Summary The Monthly Vulnerability Summary report provides summary headline, distribution, and trending data for vulnerabilities found across your environment. The report provides the following:
Vulnerability status and vulnerable hosts counts Severity and age distribution Categorized trends Top 10 lists Exportable vulnerability list Use this report to gain insights into the effectiveness of your current vulnerability management, learn about new vulnerabilities and emerging threats, help prioritize your efforts, and focus on specific areas in your environment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerability-top-ten/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerability-top-ten/</guid><description>Monthly Top 10 Vulnerability Lists The Monthly Top 10 Vulnerability Lists report provides top 10 lists for your most vulnerable hosts by total count and by severity, oldest critical vulnerabilities, and frequent vulnerabilities.
To access the Monthly Top 10 Vulnerability Lists report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Vulnerabilities. Under Vulnerabilities Analysis, click VIEW. Click Monthly Top 10 Vulnerability Lists.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerable-hosts-trends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/vulnerable-hosts-trends/</guid><description>Monthly Vulnerable Hosts Change Trends The Monthly Vulnerable Hosts Change Trends report contains sections that show the count and the trend of vulnerable host changes over the selected time period. You can display the data as a line or bar chart. Click the drop-down on the top right of the Vulnerable Host Count Over the Period section, and then select the chart type you want to see.
To access the Vulnerable Hosts Change Trends report:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/weekly-vulnerability-distribution-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/weekly-vulnerability-distribution-explorer/</guid><description>Weekly Vulnerability Distribution Explorer The Weekly Vulnerability Distribution Explorer report provides insights into patterns from the vulnerabilities found in your environment, including vulnerability distribution and trends categorized by status, exploitability, severity, age, operating system, and asset type. Use this report to help you optimize your vulnerability management process.
To access the Weekly Vulnerability Distribution Explorer report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/weekly-vulnerability-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/weekly-vulnerability-summary/</guid><description>Weekly Vulnerability Summary The Weekly Vulnerability Summary report provides summary headline, distribution, and trending data for vulnerabilities found across your environment. The report provides the following:
Vulnerability status and vulnerable hosts counts Severity and age distribution Categorized trends Top 10 lists Exportable vulnerability list Use this report to gain insights into the effectiveness of your current vulnerability management, learn about new vulnerabilities and emerging threats, help prioritize your efforts, and focus on specific areas in your environment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/weekly-vulnerability-top-ten/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/weekly-vulnerability-top-ten/</guid><description>Weekly Top 10 Vulnerability Lists The Weekly Top 10 Vulnerability Lists report provides top 10 lists for your most vulnerable hosts by total count and by severity, oldest critical vulnerabilities, and frequent vulnerabilities.
To access the Weekly Top 10 Vulnerability Lists report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Vulnerabilities. Under Vulnerabilities Analysis, click VIEW. Click Weekly Top 10 Vulnerability Lists.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/weekly-vulnerability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/vulnerability-analysis/weekly-vulnerability/</guid><description>Weekly Vulnerability Analysis The Weekly Vulnerability Analysis report provides insights into vulnerabilities and vulnerable assets found in your environment, including vulnerabilities by severity and age, vulnerability trends, vulnerabilities by day and severity, and top vulnerable hosts, networks, and deployment lists for the selected week. Use this report to gain insights into the effectiveness of your vulnerability management, help prioritize your efforts, and focus on specific areas in your environment.
This report presents data for an entire week, from Monday through Sunday, which immediately becomes available in the beginning of the following week.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/weekly-vulnerability-variance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/vulnerabilities/weekly-vulnerability-variance/</guid><description>Weekly Vulnerability Variance The Weekly Vulnerability Variance report provides a comparison of total unresolved, new, and resolved vulnerability instances in your environment from the previous week. Use this report to gain insights into the effectiveness of your vulnerability management and remediation efforts.
To access the Weekly Vulnerability Variance report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click Vulnerabilities. Under Vulnerability Variance, click VIEW.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/waf/reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/waf/reports/</guid><description>WAF Reports The REPORTS page in the Alert Logic console provides access to data related to exposures and incidents Alert Logic found within your deployments. You can also view data related to your product usage within your accounts. For information on all the available report groups, see Reports Guide.
To access the WAF reports, in the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate. Click Reports, and then click WAF.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/waf/waf-activity-report/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/waf/waf-activity-report/</guid><description>WAF Activity Report The WAF Activity report provides information on activity being validated by the Alert Logic Managed Web Application Firewall (WAF). Use the report to evaluate WAF activity by attack class, risk level, violation description, and website activity.
The Activity Report provides a filtered report on activity during a slice of time.
To access the WAF activity report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/waf/waf-policy-report/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/reports/waf/waf-policy-report/</guid><description>WAF Policy Report The WAF Policy report provides a summary of the Alert Logic Managed Web Application Firewall (WAF) security configuration on a per website basis. Each PCI Policy report provides the security policy settings for a single website protected by the WAF. Use this report to review policy settings across appliances and websites.
To access the WAF Policy report:
In the Alert Logic console, click the menu icon (), and then click Validate.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/downloads/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/downloads/</guid><description>Downloads The Search experience in the Alert Logic console is intended to allow you to perform basic and advanced searches for different data types. The Search feature is flexible for structuring advanced search queries, and using fields and predefined expressions to help you find and organize messages most relevant to your investigation.
From the Downloads page in Search, you can view and manage the list of searches generated by a search schedule you previously saved and scheduled.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/expert-mode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/expert-mode/</guid><description>Search Expert Mode The Search experience in the Alert Logic console is intended to allow you to perform basic in Simple mode and advance searches in Expert mode for different data types. Simple mode allows you to add or remove conditions and fields, aggregate or add a function to predefined expressions, and determine sorting and order. For more information about Search Simple Mode, see Search Simple Mode .
Expert mode allows you to create your own SQL searches and aggregations.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/fim-search-examples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/fim-search-examples/</guid><description>File Integrity Monitoring (FIM) Search Examples The Alert Logic Search experience allows you to search for File Integrity Monitoring events as fimdata data types. The following examples illustrate a few common searches for File Integrity Monitoring (FIM) data type search. You can copy the search, and then substitute objects with your own to structure query searches relevant to your organization and its security goals.
The following are reminders to successfully execute a search:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/help/</guid><description>Search Help Query Builder The Search experience in the Alert Logic console is intended to allow you to perform basic and advanced searches for different data types. The Search feature is flexible for structuring advanced search queries, and using fields and predefined expressions to help you find and organize messages most relevant to your investigation.
The Alert Logic console provides a help library of search fields that you can use to add to your query in Search in Expert mode.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/manage-search-results/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/manage-search-results/</guid><description>Manage Search Results Messages The Search experience in the Alert Logic console is intended to allow you to perform basic and advanced searches for different data types. The Search feature is flexible for structuring advanced search queries, and using fields and predefined expressions to help you find and organize messages most relevant to your investigation.
To access the Search page, click the menu icon (), and then click Investigate. Click Search, and then click the Search tab.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/save-schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/save-schedule/</guid><description>Saved and Scheduled Searches The Search experience in the Alert Logic console is intended to allow you to perform basic and advanced searches for different data types. The Search feature is flexible for structuring advanced search queries, and using fields and predefined expressions to help you find and organize messages most relevant to your investigation.
Alert Logic saves your recent executed searches and allows you to save and schedule any search for frequent use.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/schedule-searches/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/schedule-searches/</guid><description>Schedule Search Notification The Search page in the Alert Logic console allows you to perform basic and advance searches for different log messages data types that can help you find and organize messages most relevant to your investigation. You can schedule a weekly or monthly log searches for your different data types, and be notified when the search is complete. The search and notification can help you keep records and track any changes.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/search-correlation-examples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/search-correlation-examples/</guid><description>Examples of Search Correlation Queries The improved correlation experience allows you to create powerful custom rules with similar syntax structure as Search queries in the Search page of the Alert Logic console. When you create a correlations rule, Alert Logic examines data as it is collected for matching patterns based on the correlation alert you created and will trigger an incident or an alert. For more information on Search Correlations, see Improved Correlations and Search.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/search-correlation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/search-correlation/</guid><description>Improved Correlations and Search Correlations help you detect security weaknesses or threats for further investigation and response from custom logic you create to meet the specific security needs of your company or the accounts you manage. The improved correlation experience allows you to create powerful custom rules with similar syntax structure as Search queries in the Get Started with Search page of the Alert Logic console. When you create a correlation rule, Alert Logic examines data as it is collected for matching patterns based on the correlation alert you created and will trigger an incident or an alert.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/search-examples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/search-examples/</guid><description>Search SQL Reference The following examples illustrate a few common searches. You can copy the search, and then substitute log message objects with your own to create searches relevant to your organization and its security goals.
In the new Search experience, there some changes to keep in mind to execute successful searched:
Strings are &amp;lsquo;single quoted&amp;rsquo; Field names (and aliases) are &amp;ldquo;double quoted&amp;rdquo;. Double quoting can be used to access fields with the same name as SQL reserved words, like &amp;ldquo;count&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/simple-mode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/search/simple-mode/</guid><description>Search Simple Mode The Search experience in the Alert Logic console is intended to allow you to perform basic in Simple mode and advance searches in Expert mode for different data types.
Simple mode provides a graphical interface that allows you to add or remove conditions and fields, aggregate or add a function to predefined expressions, and determine sorting and order. Simple mode is optimized for performing common types of search queries.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/security-incidents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/security-incidents/</guid><description>Authentication Application Security Incidents Alert Logic can detect and generate security incidents from log data collected from third-party authentication application resources. Alert Logic collects log data through API-based integration with these applications. Authentication security incidents enhances your security content by providing greater visibility into threats in your environment.
Security incidents are generated when suspicious events are detected that require attention to maintain your security posture, achieve regulatory compliance, or both. Alert Logic organizes the incidents by threat level and classification type on your Incidents page.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/security-posture-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/security-posture-dashboard/</guid><description>Security Posture Dashboard In early 2020, the Security Posture dashboard was deprecated. The information is still available on the Threat Risk Index Summary.
Alert Logic provides an overview of the current state of your environments when you log into the Alert Logic console. The Security Posture page, under the Overview tab in the Alert Logic console, displays interactive dashboard summaries of your environment for Threat Risk Index (TRI), Remediations, and if you have an Alert Logic Professional or Alert Logic Enterprise subscription, for Incidents.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/service-status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/service-status/</guid><description>Service Status The Alert Logic Service Status page allows customers to monitor the status of their subscribed region and product capabilities. Alert Logic provides updates for incidents in progress, including the overall status of Alert Logic regions and products, statuses for individual product capabilities, and details about past incidents. Alert Logic customers can also subscribe to notifications when Alert Logic creates, updates, or resolves an incident.
To access the Service Status page, in the Alert Logic console, open the Manage menu item, and then select Service Status.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intel-center/about-analytics-content/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intel-center/about-analytics-content/</guid><description>About Analytics in the Threat Intelligence Center The Threat Intelligence Center provides a tabular list for the properties of each analytic available from Alert Logic. Use the analytics view in the Threat Intelligence Center to validate Alert Logic threat coverage, learn about analytics content, investigate content configuration requirements, and source information for automated response. To learn more about the Threat Intelligence Center, see Threat Intelligence Center (Beta).
Learn about analytics An Alert Logic analytic is a rule-based or machine learning algorithm that uses telemetry data to evaluate activity to produce incidents or observations.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intel-center/about-ids-signature-content/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intel-center/about-ids-signature-content/</guid><description>About IDS Signatures in the Threat Intelligence Center The Threat Intelligence Center provides a tabular list for the properties of each IDS signature available from Alert Logic. Use the IDS signatures view in the Threat Intelligence Center to learn about IDS signature content. To learn more about the Threat Intelligence Center, see Threat Intelligence Center (Beta).
Learn about IDS signatures Network traffic is the machine-to-machine activity to and from your environment, and it is monitored by the Network IDS appliance.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intel-center/about-log-parser-content/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intel-center/about-log-parser-content/</guid><description>About Log Parsers in the Threat Intelligence Center The Threat Intelligence Center provides a tabular list for the properties of each log parser available from Alert Logic. Use the log parsers view in the Threat Intelligence Center to learn about log parser content. To learn more about the Threat Intelligence Center, see Threat Intelligence Center (Beta).
Learn about log parsers Logs are messages that function as a ledger for activity generated by applications in a system.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intel-center/analytics-ga-dump/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intel-center/analytics-ga-dump/</guid><description>analytics-GA-dump Content Types Information here about how each content type has it&amp;rsquo;s own experience
Analytics IDS Signatures Log Parsers Vulnerability Library Provide content information to Auditors:
View an overall picture of content Validate that content is being updated on your appliances View details of individual pieces of content Validate that Alert Logic is covering specific vulnerabilities:
Search a vulnerability by name See if you are vulnerable Learn how long a vulnerability has existed in your environment Learn if an attack using the vulnerability has been detected Gather information for Incident response:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intel-center/archived-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intel-center/archived-beta/</guid><description>Threat Intelligence Center (Beta) This document is intended for early-access customers, and it is updated as Threat Intelligence Center features are enhanced. The Threat Intelligence Center provides insight into Alert Logic content coverage by displaying security content details in an interactive table. Use the Threat Intelligence Center to validate Alert Logic threat coverage, learn about analytics content, investigate content configuration requirements, and source information for automated response.
Information in the Threat Intelligence Center is not specific to your environment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intel-center/threat-classifications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intel-center/threat-classifications/</guid><description>Threat Classifications The following table lists and defines the possible classification types.
Classification label in Alert Logic console Classification Description application-attack Application attack An application attack incident identifies attacks that target application-specific vulnerabilities. Alert Logic creates an application attack incident when an attacker attempts to compromise an application with a buffer overflow, race condition, directory traversal, SQL injection, cross-site scripting, or /usr/bin/perl or other UNIX command attempts. admin:activity Admin activity An authentication security incident identified from security applications is related specifically to administrative actions.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intelligence-center/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-intelligence-center/</guid><description>Threat Intelligence Center (Beta) This document is intended for early-access customers, and it is updated as Threat Intelligence Center features are enhanced. The Threat Intelligence Center provides insight into Alert Logic threat coverage by displaying security content details in an interactive, tabular list. You can use the Threat Intelligence Center to learn technical details about how Alert Logic analyzes data to produce security outcomes, using different types of security content. The Threat Intelligence Center displays all customer agnostic security content and coverage details provided by Alert Logic and you can use it to help determine if your environment is configured to maximize security value.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-summary-csh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/threat-summary-csh/</guid><description>Threat Summary The Threat Summary dashboard provides visibility into threats and incidents in your environment. Use this dashboard to gain insights into the types of incidents that were detected, analyze the effectiveness of your current incident response efforts, and learn about emerging threats. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Current count of open incidents in every threat level. Current count of incident in each threat level. Trend of incidents by threat level over the course of the last 30 days.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/topology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/topology/</guid><description>Topology The Topology page, under the Investigate menu item, displays an interactive diagram that uses color-coded icons to show the distribution of exposures and threats across your network assets.
Topology allows you to select regions or assets to see details about the item, exposures, and remediations for those exposures.
Topology page The Topology page header allows you to specify a deployment and a region, and displays the number of VPCs, VNETs or networks, subnets, and hosts in that selected deployment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/tri-score-factors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/tri-score-factors/</guid><description>Threat Risk Index Score Factors The Threat Risk Index (TRI) is a Alert Logic vulnerability rating system designed to help you determine which of your deployments, VPCs, or networks are most exposed and susceptible to a security attack or breach.
There are five main ways the TRI score is used in the Alert Logic console:
Per Host – A TRI score is calculated for each host, which is then used to calculate the TRI score for each VPC/network and each deployment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/vulnerability-library/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/vulnerability-library/</guid><description>Vulnerability Library A vulnerability is an important weakness to identify, as it can allow an attacker to reduce the information security of a system. Vulnerabilities are used to determine the security of your system.
Alert Logic lists all of the scan content that Alert Logic scanners can check for in the Vulnerability Library, under Investigate in the Alert Logic console. You can easily search for and view information on a specified vulnerability that Alert Logic scanned for, and see whether it impacts assets in your environment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/vulnerability-summary-csh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/analyze/vulnerability-summary-csh/</guid><description>Vulnerability Summary The Vulnerability Summary dashboard provides visibility into vulnerable software and cloud infrastructure in your environment. Use this dashboard to gain insights into the effectiveness of your current vulnerability management efforts, learn about new vulnerabilities and emerging threats, help prioritize your remediation plans, and focus on specific areas in your environment. This dashboard includes visuals of the following data:
Current count of individual vulnerabilities identified from each of your assets.</description></item></channel></rss>