<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Deploys on Hugo documentation theme</title><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/</link><description>Recent content in Deploys on Hugo documentation theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Designed by [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com) &amp; Developed by [Gethugothemes](https://gethugothemes.com)</copyright><atom:link href="https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/about-appliances/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/about-appliances/</guid><description>Deployments: Appliances The Alert Logic appliance is available as an on-premise physical device, or available for download for Alert Logic deployments on virtual machines.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/about-scans/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/about-scans/</guid><description>About Alert Logic Scans A scan detects and identifies network and host vulnerabilities in your environment. Scans can perform external attack simulations as well as comprehensive vulnerability checks including registry evaluation. In Data Center deployments, discovery scans detect new assets or asset changes. Alert Logic scans can also help you meet PCI compliance requirements. To learn more about scans for PCI compliance requirements, see Manage PCI Scans.
This topic describes the types of scans that are supported, best practices for running successful scans, and how to configure and manage scan definitions and results.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/archive/about-deployments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/archive/about-deployments/</guid><description>About Alert Logic Deployment Types A deployment allows you to monitor and protect a defined set of assets from your appliances, agents, hosts, and collectors from your environments. You can create deployments for assets found in your Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Microsoft Azure cloud platforms, and from other cloud-based or physical Data Centers.
Alert Logic discovers and organizes deployments into a visual topology where you can select the desired levels of protection for your assets.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/archive/aws-auto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/archive/aws-auto/</guid><description>Amazon Web Services (AWS) Deployment Configuration—Automatic Mode Alert Logic recommends Automatic Mode for AWS deployment creation if you want Alert Logic to deploy and maintain new VPC subnets used for network IDS and scanning instances.
Deployment creation requires that you be logged into your Alert Logic account and the AWS account you want this deployment to monitor and protect.
If you manage more than one Alert Logic account, be sure you are logged into the correct account.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/archive/aws-manual/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/archive/aws-manual/</guid><description>Amazon Web Services (AWS) Deployment Configuration—Manual Mode Alert Logic allows for an optional, manual deployment mode for AWS deployments. Alert Logic recommends Manual Mode for AWS deployment creation only if you want to deploy and maintain new VPC subnets used for scanning instances.
Deployment creation requires that you be logged into your Alert Logic account and the AWS account you want this deployment to monitor and protect.
If you manage more than one Alert Logic account, be sure you are logged into the correct account.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/archive/aws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/archive/aws/</guid><description>Amazon Web Services (AWS) (AWS) Deployment Configuration Alert Logic allows you to create AWS deployments within the Alert Logic console. The Deployments page appears under the Configuration tab in the Alert Logic console. To add a deployment, click the add icon (), and then enter the requested information to provide Alert Logic with third-party access to the specified cloud environment. For more information about adding deployments for other cloud environments, see Microsoft Azure Deployment Configuration and Data Center Deployment Configuration (Essentials Subscription).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/archive/azure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/archive/azure/</guid><description>Microsoft Azure Deployment Configuration Alert Logic allows you to add Microsoft Azure deployments to the Alert Logic console. The Deployments page appears under the Configuration tab in the Alert Logic console. To add a deployment, click the add icon (), and then enter the requested information to provide Alert Logic with third-party access to the specified cloud environment. For more information about adding deployments for other cloud environments, see Amazon Web Services (AWS) (AWS) Deployment Configuration and Data Center Deployment Configuration (Essentials Subscription).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/archive/your-first-deployment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/archive/your-first-deployment/</guid><description>Your First Deployment A deployment is a set of assets from your appliances, agents, hosts, and collectors from your environments. The Deployments page under the Configuration tab in the Alert Logic console allows you to create deployments to monitor and protect your assets. You can create deployments for assets found in your Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Microsoft Azure cloud platforms, and from other cloud-based or physical Data Centers.
Alert Logic discovers and organizes deployments into a visual topology where you can select the desired levels of protection for your assets.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/aws-auto-essentials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/aws-auto-essentials/</guid><description>Amazon Web Services (AWS) Deployment Configuration—Automatic Mode (Essentials Subscription) Alert Logic recommends Automatic Mode for AWS deployment creation if you want Alert Logic to deploy and maintain new VPC subnets used for scanning instances.
Deployment creation requires that you be logged into your Alert Logic account and the AWS account you want this deployment to monitor and protect.
If you manage more than one Alert Logic account, be sure you are logged into the correct account.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/aws-auto-pro-ent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/aws-auto-pro-ent/</guid><description>Amazon Web Services (AWS) Deployment Configuration—Automatic Mode (Professional Subscription) Alert Logic recommends Automatic Mode for AWS deployment creation if you want Alert Logic to deploy and maintain new VPC subnets used for network IDS and scanning instances.
Deployment creation requires that you be logged into your Alert Logic account and the AWS account you want this deployment to monitor and protect.
If you manage more than one Alert Logic account, be sure you are logged into the correct account.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/aws-control-tower/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/aws-control-tower/</guid><description>Deployment with AWS Control Tower Customers who use AWS Control Tower and Alert Logic can get automatic protection of existing and newly enrolled accounts through a series of automations.
Architecture The Alert Logic Control Tower Automation uses the following AWS Services to enable automatic protection of newly added AWS Accounts:
Amazon EventBridge AWS CloudFormation AWS Lambda Cross-account IAM Roles AWS Secrets Manager Amazon SNS Amazon SQS Accounts shown in the architecture diagram:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/aws-manual-essentials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/aws-manual-essentials/</guid><description>Amazon Web Services (AWS) Deployment Configuration—Manual Mode (Essentials Subscription) Alert Logic allows for an optional, manual deployment mode for AWS deployments. Alert Logic recommends Manual Mode for AWS deployment creation only if you want to deploy and maintain scanning instances in your deployments.
Deployment creation requires that you be logged into your Alert Logic account and the AWS account you want this deployment to monitor and protect.
If you manage more than one Alert Logic account, be sure you are logged into the correct account.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/aws-manual-pro-ent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/aws-manual-pro-ent/</guid><description>Amazon Web Services (AWS) Deployment Configuration—Manual Mode (Professional Subscription) Alert Logic allows for an optional, manual deployment mode for AWS deployments. Alert Logic recommends Manual Mode for AWS deployment creation only if you want to deploy and maintain scanning instances in your deployments.
Deployment creation requires that you be logged into your Alert Logic account and the AWS account you want this deployment to monitor and protect.
If you manage more than one Alert Logic account, be sure you are logged into the correct account.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/azure-essentials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/azure-essentials/</guid><description>Microsoft Azure Deployment Configuration (Essentials Subscription) Alert Logic allows you to add Microsoft Azure deployments to the Alert Logic console. You can access the Deployments page from the Configure menu item in the Alert Logic console. To add a deployment, click the add icon (), and then enter the requested information to provide Alert Logic with third-party access to the specified cloud environment.
Name your deployment In the Deployment Name field, type a descriptive name for the deployment you want to create, and then click SAVE AND CONTINUE.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/azure-pro-ent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/azure-pro-ent/</guid><description>Microsoft Azure Deployment Configuration (Professional Subscription) Alert Logic allows you to add Microsoft Azure deployments to the Alert Logic console. You can access the Deployments page from the Configure menu item in the Alert Logic console. To add a deployment, click the add icon (), and then enter the requested information to provide Alert Logic with third-party access to the specified cloud environment.
Name your deployment In the Deployment Name field, type a descriptive name for the deployment you want to create, and then click SAVE AND CONTINUE.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/change-protection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/change-protection/</guid><description>Change Protection Level of an Asset When you create a deployment, Alert Logic prompts you to assign the scope of protection for each asset included in the deployment. Your subscription determines the level of protection you can assign to the assets. You can change protection levels as your needs or entitlements change.
Alert Logic discovers and organizes deployments into a visual topology where you can select the desired levels of protection for your assets.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/cross-network-protection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/cross-network-protection/</guid><description>Cross-Network Protection Alert Logic allows you to set up Cross-Network Protection from a manual deployment in the Alert Logic console. Cross-Network Protection creates connections across networks, in the same or different deployment, that use resources from a protecting network to protect other networks within the same account.
Cross-Network Protection allows an assigned network appliance, for Network IDS or scanning, to reside outside the protected network. This centralizes the appliances that provide protection to an account, which allows your organization to reduce infrastructure costs.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/data-center-essentials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/data-center-essentials/</guid><description>Data Center Deployment Configuration (Essentials Subscription) Alert Logic allows you to add deployments to the Alert Logic console. You can access the Deployments page from the Configure menu item in the Alert Logic console. To add a Data Center deployment, click the add icon (), and then click Data Center.
Name your deployment In the Deployment Name field, type a descriptive name for the deployment you want to create, and then click SAVE AND CONTINUE.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/data-center-pro-ent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/data-center-pro-ent/</guid><description>Data Center Deployment Configuration (Professional Subscription) Alert Logic allows you to add deployments to the Alert Logic console. You can access the Deployments page from the Configure menu item in the Alert Logic console. To add a Data Center deployment, click the add icon (), and then click Data Center.
Name your deployment In the Deployment Name field, type a descriptive name for the deployment you want to create, and then click SAVE AND CONTINUE.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/deployment-assets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/deployment-assets/</guid><description>Deployment Assets introduction here
Networks A network is a range of IP addresses, expressed in CIDR notation, that you want to monitor within your network. A network cannot monitor a range of IP addresses larger than a /8 CIDR.
To monitor a network, you must apply the network to a monitoring policy. You may apply multiple networks to a monitoring policy. For more information about monitoring policies, see .
Create and protect networks The networks feature allows you to create and protect networks.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/endpoint-installer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/endpoint-installer/</guid><description>Deploy Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection Extended Endpoint Protection is built to provide value and scale immediately. You can silently install the agent on many endpoints in minutes using any tool that supports deploying EXE or MSI files, including system management tools or Windows Group Policy. Once you deploy Extended Endpoint Protection, the endpoints automatically register, and you can manage them in the Alert Logic console.
Install Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection The Extended Endpoint Protection installer is available in the Alert Logic console on the Endpoints page.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/google-cloud-essentials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/google-cloud-essentials/</guid><description>Data Center Deployment Configuration for Google Cloud Platform (Essentials Subscription) Alert Logic allows you to use a Data Center deployment to monitor your assets on the Google Cloud Platform. Before your deployment can monitor your assets, you must install an Alert Logic appliance and agents to your Google Cloud environment.
Before you begin Before you create your first Data Center deployment for Google Cloud Platform, you must:
Install the gcloud command line tool for use with your GCP account.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/google-cloud-pro-ent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/google-cloud-pro-ent/</guid><description>Data Center Deployment for Google Cloud Platform (Professional Subscription) Alert Logic allows you to use a Data Center deployment to monitor your assets on the Google Cloud Platform. Before your deployment can monitor your assets, you must install an Alert Logic appliance and agents to your Google Cloud environment.
Before you begin Before you create your first Data Center deployment for Google Cloud Platform, you must:
Install the gcloud command line tool for use with your GCP account.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/log-sources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/log-sources/</guid><description>Log Sources A log source is a software or hardware component that produces log data. Multiple types of sources exist, and multiple methods exist to retrieve log data from the sources. The Alert Logic console allows you to create, edit, and update log sources, archive or restore old sources, and perform other tasks.
Supported log sources Alert Logic supports log source types for all deployments, including Data Center, Amazon Web Services (AWS), and Microsoft Azure.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/log-sources/log-sources-all-deployments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/log-sources/log-sources-all-deployments/</guid><description>Configure Log Sources for All Deployments Alert Logic supports the following log source types for all deployments, including Data Center:
All deployments:
Flat File logs—Log messages stored in flat text files collected by an Alert Logic agent or appliance
Syslog—A way for network devices to send event messages to a logging server
You cannot create a Syslog source through the Alert Logic console. You can only do so if you install an agent on a supported *NIX system or if you configure a source device to send messages in the RFC 5424 Syslog format to an Alert Logic appliance or remote collector.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/log-sources/log-sources-aws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/log-sources/log-sources-aws/</guid><description>Configure Log Sources for Amazon Web Services (AWS) Alert Logic supports the following log source types for AWS deployments:
AWS CloudTrail logs—Log messages generated by the AWS CloudTrail service that record AWS API activity in your account AWS S3 logs—Log records that provide details about a single access request, such as the requester, bucket name, request time, request action, response status, and any error codes For more information about other log source types, see Configure Log Sources for All Deployments or Configure Log Sources for Microsoft Azure.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/log-sources/log-sources-azure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/log-sources/log-sources-azure/</guid><description>Configure Log Sources for Microsoft Azure Alert Logic supports the following log source types for Azure:
Azure Activity logs—Logs that provide insight into the operations performed on resources in your subscription Azure App Service web server logs—Logs that provide detailed error information for HTTP failure status codes, failed requests, or HTTP transactions using the W3C extended log file format Set up collection of Microsoft Office 365 Logs—Activity logs that provide information including administrative, user, and policy actions Azure SQL auditing logs—Logs that provide information on database events Alert Logic Log Collector for Microsoft Azure Event Hubs—Logs collected by Azure Event Hubs, which streams Azure Active Directory logs, Diagnostic Activity logs, Security Center logs, and SQL Audit logs to Alert Logic For more information about other log source types, see Configure Log Sources for All Deployments or Configure Log Sources for Amazon Web Services (AWS).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/manage-scans-results/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/manage-scans-results/</guid><description>How to work with scans and scan results You can access detailed information about network and host vulnerabilities discovered during internal and external scans from the Scans tab on the Scans page in the Alert Logic console. From the Scans tab, you can create new scans, edit existing scan definitions, and view scan results.
For information about PCI scans, see Manage PCI scans.
Access Alert Logic scans You can access most scan-related features from the Scans page in the Alert Logic console.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/networks/</guid><description>Configure and Manage Networks in Data Center Deployments A network is a range of IP addresses, expressed in CIDR notation, that you want an appliance to monitor. You can configure a network with a CIDR range up to /8. However, Alert Logic recommends that you configure networks with the smallest subnet blocks that match your environment. Doing so improves visibility into network traffic levels and improves the ability to monitor the health of your environment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/oracle-cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/oracle-cloud/</guid><description>Alert Logic Data Center Deployment for Oracle Cloud Oracle Cloud Platform is a comprehensive, standards-based combination of Oracle3 and open source technologies to enable you to more efficiently build, deploy, integrate, secure and manage all your enterprise applications.
Alert Logic allows you to use a Data Center deployment to monitor your assets on the Oracle Cloud Platform. Before your deployment can monitor your assets, you must install an Alert Logic appliance and agents to your Oracle Cloud environment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/test-endpoint-protection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/test-endpoint-protection/</guid><description>Test Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection Extended Endpoint Protection focuses on what attackers cannot disguise and what traditional endpoint solutions cannot observe: the attributes and behaviors of malware at runtime. This means Alert Logic does not take action against malware that is killed by another tool pre-execution or against unexecuted malware. Instead, Extended Endpoint Protection takes action when malware gets past other layers and attempts to detonate.
Testing tools from Alert Logic To demonstrate effectiveness, Alert Logic provides these testing tools that simulate the behavior of ransomware and credential theft malware.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/vdi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/deploy/vdi/</guid><description>Virtual Desktop Infrastructure Environments You can install Extended Endpoint Protection on virtual machines that are part of a virtual desktop infrastructure (VDI) environment.
The two most common VDI setups are:
VMware Horizon View Citrix XenDesktop Extended Endpoint Protection is only available for the following VDI workstations:
Windows 7 Windows 8.1 Windows 10 macOS High Sierra macOS Mojave macOS Catalina Deploy Extended Endpoint Protection with VDI When you install Extended Endpoint Protection on an endpoint, the agent contacts Alert Logic, and Alert Logic assigns the endpoint a unique identifier.</description></item></channel></rss>