<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Best-practices on Hugo documentation theme</title><link>https://richg-github.github.io/sdk.github.io/best-practices/</link><description>Recent content in Best-practices on Hugo documentation theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Designed by [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com) &amp; Developed by [Gethugothemes](https://gethugothemes.com)</copyright><atom:link href="https://richg-github.github.io/sdk.github.io/best-practices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/sdk.github.io/best-practices/log-management-bp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/sdk.github.io/best-practices/log-management-bp/</guid><description>Log Management Best Practices Configuring log management systems has become more complex as elaborate networks and increased regulatory requirements demand a more complex log management setup. Log management now extends beyond simple data collection; it encompasses normalization, analysis, reporting, and disaster-proof archival processes. The expansion of IT infrastructure into hosted and cloud deployments means you have more data to manage, and that data resides in a variety of environments.
These emerging challenges require that you configure your log management practices to focus on several key areas:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/sdk.github.io/best-practices/log-management-challenges/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/sdk.github.io/best-practices/log-management-challenges/</guid><description>Log Management Challenges Many compliance mandates, such as PCI DSS, require not only that you collect all logs, but that they be reviewed regularly, are searchable, and are stored in their original, unaltered, raw form for mandate-specific timeframes.
Logs can also be extremely useful in identifying security incidents, policy violations, fraudulent activity, and operational problems shortly after they occur. They are extremely valuable when performing audits, forensic analysis, internal investigations, establishing baselines, and identifying operational trends and long-term problems.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/sdk.github.io/best-practices/log-management-log-collection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/sdk.github.io/best-practices/log-management-log-collection/</guid><description>Log Management—Which Logs to Collect To meet regulatory compliance standards, all logs must be collected—not just the security logs. For example, operating system logs and application logs often contain security-related information and information about events that may not initially appear security related. Organizations must consider the potential value of each possible log source. Consider the following log types for collection:
Anti-malware software logs include indicators that malware was detected, disinfection attempt results, file quarantines, when file-system scans were last performed, when anti-virus signature files were last updated, and when software upgrades have taken place.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/sdk.github.io/best-practices/log-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/sdk.github.io/best-practices/log-management/</guid><description>Log Management Best Practices Compliance requirements drive the need for log management. Regulations and standards require log collection, retention, and access for routine log analysis. You also need complete visibility into the assets you manage in cloud platforms. Routine log analysis can help you with the following security tasks:
Identify security incidents Prevent policy violations Monitor and detect fraudulent activities Establish performance baselines Perform auditing and forensic analysis Support internal investigations Identify operational trends and long-term problems Most compliance mandates require that you regularly review collected logs.</description></item></channel></rss>