<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Product-guides on Hugo documentation theme</title><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/product-guides/</link><description>Recent content in Product-guides on Hugo documentation theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Designed by [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com) &amp; Developed by [Gethugothemes](https://gethugothemes.com)</copyright><atom:link href="https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/product-guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/product-guides/blockingconfig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/product-guides/blockingconfig/</guid><description>Blocking Configuration Blocking Configuration is a Network IDS configuration that allows you to set up blocks to prevent attackers from accessing your network. This functionality requires a physical appliance.
To access Blocking Configuration, click CONFIGURATION and Network IDS. Blocking Configuration appears in the left navigation area.
Items to configure before you set up automated blocking policies Automated blocking policies require the following configurations.
Complete these configuration items in the order provided.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/product-guides/cloud-insight/cloud-insight-upgrade-downgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/product-guides/cloud-insight/cloud-insight-upgrade-downgrade/</guid><description>Change the Assessment Level of a Cloud Insight Deployment If you want to enable scanning for a Cloud Insight Essentials deployment, or disable scanning for a Cloud Insight deployment, Alert Logic allows you to do so quickly through the Deployments page.
Upgrade from Cloud Insight Essentials to Cloud Insight To enable scanning for a Cloud Insight Essentials deployment, you can edit the security policy in AWS. Then, in Cloud Insight Essentials, edit the deployment and change the level of assessment to Cloud Insight.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/product-guides/console/incidents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/product-guides/console/incidents/</guid><description>Incidents Overview Alert Logic Cloud Defender and Alert Logic Cloud Insight Essentials display information about incidents, how to use that information to manage and close incidents, and how to secure your environments.
An incident comprises correlated suspicious events that require attention to maintain your security posture, achieve regulatory compliance, or both. Alert Logic generates incidents based on various predefined scenarios.
In addition, Alert Logic uses evidence received from monitored assets to classify threats by the type of attack they represent and to assign a threat level to the incident.</description></item></channel></rss>