<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Requirements on Hugo documentation theme</title><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/</link><description>Recent content in Requirements on Hugo documentation theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Designed by [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com) &amp; Developed by [Gethugothemes](https://gethugothemes.com)</copyright><atom:link href="https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/agent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/agent/</guid><description>Requirements for the Alert Logic Agent The following table describes the basic requirements to install the agent:
Processors supported by the agent:
Intel ARM Operating systems supported by the agent:
For Windows users: Windows Server 2003, SP1 Windows Server 2008 Windows Server 2012 Windows Server 2016 Windows Server 2019 Windows Server 20H2 Windows Vista Windows 7 Windows 8 Windows XP SP1 Windows 10 For Linux users: Debian (.deb) 5.x (lenny) 6.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/amazon-web-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/amazon-web-services/</guid><description>Requirements for Managed Detection and Response for Amazon Web Services (AWS) Supported AWS regions Alert Logic supports the following AWS regions:
AWS Region Name Region Endpoint Africa (Cape Town) af-south-1 Asia Pacific (Hong Kong) ap-east-1 rds.ap-east-1.amazonaws.com Asia Pacific (Tokyo) ap-northeast-1 autoscaling.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com Asia Pacific (Seoul) ap-northeast-2 autoscaling.ap-northeast-2.amazonaws.com Asia Pacific (Osaka-Local) ap-northeast-3 ec2.eu-west-3.amazonaws.com Asia Pacific (Mumbai) ap-south-1 autoscaling.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com Asia Pacific (Singapore) ap-southeast-1 autoscaling.ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com Asia Pacific (Sydney) ap-southeast-2 autoscaling.ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com Canada (Central) ca-central-1 autoscaling.ca-central-1.amazonaws.com China (Beijing) cn-north-1 ec2.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/appliance-requirements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/appliance-requirements/</guid><description>Alert Logic Requirements for Virtual and Physical Appliances Requirements for Alert Logic IDS virtual appliances Bandwidth volume directly impacts the ability of the appliance to inspect traffic. High-traffic environments may require a virtual machine with additional processor and memory resources.
The following table describes the basic system requirements to install a virtual IDS appliance:
Virtual CPU cores Components System Requirements 4 cores RAM 16 GB Disk space 40 GB minimum Supported virtual environment VMware and Hyper-V Encryption TLS Standard (SSL): 2048-bit key encryption, 256-bit AES bulk encryption Peak supported throughput 500 Mbps 8 cores RAM 32 GB Disk space 40 GB minimum Supported virtual environment VMware and Hyper-V Encryption TLS Standard (SSL): 2048-bit key encryption, 256-bit AES bulk encryption Peak supported throughput 1 Gbps 16 cores RAM 64 GB Disk space 40 GB minimum Supported virtual environment VMware and Hyper-V Encryption TLS Standard (SSL): 2048-bit key encryption, 256-bit AES bulk encryption Peak supported throughput 2 Gbps (1 Gbps per fiber interface) Physical IDS appliance specifications Bandwidth volume directly impacts the ability of the appliance to inspect traffic.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/endpoint-requirements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/endpoint-requirements/</guid><description>Requirements for Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection System requirements Operating systems Extended Endpoint Protection supports the following operating systems:
Workstations Windows 7 Windows 8.1 Windows 10 macOS 10.13 - 11.x Servers Windows Server 2008 R2 Windows Server 2012 Windows Server 2016 Windows Server 2019 Hardware Extended Endpoint Protection supports the following processors:
64-bit operating systems running on 64-bit processors Windows 7 32-bit operating systems Intel processors AMD processors OS language support The application supports the following OS-level language settings:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/google-cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/google-cloud/</guid><description>Requirements for Managed Detection and Response for Google Cloud Platform Before you begin with Google Cloud Platform, you must:
Install the gcloud command-line tool to use with your GCP account. For more information about the gcloud CLI, see this Google Cloud Platform document. Configure your system to launch and use Jinja templates. Instance type sizes The following table shows the instance sizes and types that the Alert Logic image can use in GCP:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/microsoft-azure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/microsoft-azure/</guid><description>Requirements for Managed Detection and Response for Microsoft Azure Virtual IDS and Scanner appliance requirements The following provides requirement information to install an Alert Logic IDS virtual and scanner appliance in an Azure environment.
Virtual IDS appliance Use the following information to determine your virtual machine size requirements.
Throughput calculation Use the following calculation to get the virtual appliance throughput requirements. The result of this calculation provides the information you need to determine the correct instance type size to select during the installation procedure.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/operating-system-browsers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/operating-system-browsers/</guid><description>Operating System and Browser Requirements Operating system and browser support The Alert Logic console supports the current version and the previous major version of the following operating systems:
Mac Linux Windows The Alert Logic console supports the current version and the previous major version of the following browsers:
Chrome Safari Firefox Microsoft Edge Opera Internet Explorer Alert Logic cannot guarantee that other browsers and versions will work with its products.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/oracle-cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/oracle-cloud/</guid><description>Requirements for Managed Detection and Response for Oracle Cloud Instance type sizes The following tables show the instance sizes and types that Alert LogicEssentials, Professional and Enterprise customers can use in Oracle Cloud:
| Size | Instance type
Essentials performance | Size | Instance type
Professional performance | Size | Instance type
Enterprise performance The actual performance for your deployment depends on factors such as request size, complexity, and the ratio of inbound to outbound traffic.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/remote-collector/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/remote-collector/</guid><description>Requirements for the Alert Logic Remote Collector The following describes the basic requirements to install a remote collector:
Components System Requirements CPU 2 cores RAM 2 GB Disk space 10 GB minimum Supported Operating Systems Windows and Linux Log collection support Syslog only via port 1515 Encryption TLS Standard (SSL): 2048-bit key encryption, 256-bit AES bulk encryption Log collection frequency Every five minutes (minimum)- logs collected and sent to Alert Logic Cloud Host permissions LocalSystem account has all the requisite permissions by default Firewall rules For more information on firewall rules for remote collectors, see United States Firewall Rules or United Kingdom and European Union Firewall Rules.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/system-requirements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/system-requirements/</guid><description>System Requirements Operating system and browser support The Alert Logic console supports the current version and the previous major version of the following operating systems:
Mac Linux Windows The Alert Logic console supports the current version and the previous major version of the following browsers:
Chrome Safari Firefox Microsoft Edge Opera Internet Explorer Alert Logic cannot guarantee that other browsers and versions will work with its products.
Requirements for the Alert Logic agent The following table describes the basic requirements to install the agent:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/uk-eu-firewall-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/uk-eu-firewall-rules/</guid><description>United Kingdom and European Union Firewall Rules Before installing Alert Logic products, you need to adjust your firewall rules so that data can be securely transferred to and from Alert Logic, along with allowing product updates to occur.
Communication with Alert Logic Network IDSappliances Appliance inbound Depending on your environment and default firewall rules, additional rules may be required to allow the Alert Logic EU data center to communicate with the Alert Logic appliances.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/us-firewall-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/requirements/us-firewall-rules/</guid><description>United States Firewall Rules Before you install Alert Logic products, you need to adjust your firewall rules so that data can be securely transferred to and from Alert Logic, along with allowing product updates to occur.
Communication with Alert Logic Network IDS appliances Appliance inbound Depending on your environment and default firewall rules, additional rules may be required to allow the Alert Logic US data center to communicate with the Alert Logic appliances.</description></item></channel></rss>