<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Get-starteds on Hugo documentation theme</title><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/</link><description>Recent content in Get-starteds on Hugo documentation theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Designed by [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com) &amp; Developed by [Gethugothemes](https://gethugothemes.com)</copyright><atom:link href="https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/about-deployment-types/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/about-deployment-types/</guid><description>About Deployment Types A deployment allows you to monitor and protect a defined set of assets from your appliances, agents, hosts, and collectors from your environments. You can create deployments for assets found in your Amazon Web Services (AWS), Microsoft Azure, and other cloud-based or physical data centers.
Alert Logic discovers and organizes deployments into a visual topology where you can select the desired levels of protection for your assets. You must choose one of the following levels of coverage for each asset:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/about-extended-endpoint-protection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/about-extended-endpoint-protection/</guid><description>About Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection The Extended Endpoint Protection functionality from Alert Logic helps you control threats and manage incidents from employee workstations, points of sale, servers, and more.
Blocks multi-vector attacks The Alert Logic Rapidvisor agent combines machine learning attribute analysis and dynamic behavior analysis to detect complex attack techniques, including exploits, malicious scripts, and malicious executables. The agent continuously monitors system processes across user-space, the operating system, and the CPU to block malicious techniques.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/about-wla/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/about-wla/</guid><description>About Alert Logic Web Log Analytics (WLA) Alert Logic Web Log Analytics (WLA) is a log-based application attack detection solution that protects your web applications from common application vulnerabilities. WLA analyzes web server access logs for threats and attacks with a combination of pattern-matching signatures, and anomaly detection and machine-learning engine. WLA also reduces the need for tuning, minimizes false-positives, and provides visibility by inspecting HTTPS requests for threats post-decryption. You can gain security visibility across all web applications in your organization.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/amazon-web-services-cloud-insight-get-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/amazon-web-services-cloud-insight-get-started/</guid><description>Get Started with Alert Logic Cloud Insight and Cloud Insight Essentials Cloud Insight Essentials requires you perform some actions within Amazon Web Services (AWS) before Cloud Insight Essentials can start protecting your deployments. These actions and other configurations, both in AWS and in Cloud Insight Essentials, allow Alert Logic to provide you with the most relevant data you want to monitor.
About Cloud Insight Essentials deployments When you set up Cloud Insight Essentials, you create a deployment, which allows Alert Logic access to your AWS account and the services you want to monitor and protect.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/copy-of-search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/copy-of-search/</guid><description>Get Started with Search The Search experience in the Alert Logic console is intended to allows you to perform basic and advanced searches for different data types. The Search feature is flexible for structuring advanced search queries, and using fields and predefined expressions to help you find and organize messages most relevant to your investigation. Search now supports a variety of data sources that help you uncover potential threats, discover what data sources are present in an environment, and provide tools for further investigation further with the provided tools.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/deployments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/deployments/</guid><description>Get Started with Alert Logic Deployments An Alert Logic deployment allows you to specify the assets—such as appliances, agents, hosts, and collectors—in your environments to monitor and protect. You must create a deployment, regardless of your subscription level, or your assets will not be monitored or protected. You can create deployments for assets found in your Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Microsoft Azure cloud platforms, and from other cloud-based or physical data centers.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/endpoint-protection-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/endpoint-protection-upgrade/</guid><description>Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection Upgrade Alert Logic is upgrading Barkly customers to the full, robust Alert Logic Essentials subscription. This includes a number of changes to your experience. The Essentials subscription, in addition to the Extended Endpoint Protection, offers other capabilities and functionality you can use in the Alert Logic console. For more information about Alert Logic subscriptions, see Get Started with Alert Logic Subscriptions and Add-ons.
Extended Endpoint Protection changes Your new experience includes all of the same capabilities as the current Extended Endpoint Protection, including new and improved features.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/endpoint-protection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/endpoint-protection/</guid><description>Get Started with Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection Review requirements Review system requirements, communication ports, and configuration requirements for Extended Endpoint Protection.
Test Extended Endpoint Protection If you want to test Extended Endpoint Protection before you install it across your organization, refer to Test Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection.
Install Extended Endpoint Protection The Extended Endpoint Protection installer is available in the Alert Logic console on the Endpoints page.
You do not need to reinstall or upgrade the endpoint agent to receive future software updates.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/essentials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/essentials/</guid><description>Get Started with Your Alert Logic Essentials Subscription Your account subscription dictates the level of protection you can assign assets in each deployment you create. You can create deployments for assets found in your Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Microsoft Azure cloud platforms, and from other cloud-based or physical data centers.
For more information about Alert Logic subscriptions, see Alert Logic Subscription Levels.
Create your deployment When you create a deployment, the Alert Logic console prompts you through the following steps:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/get-started-cloud-defender/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/get-started-cloud-defender/</guid><description>Get started with the Alert Logic Cloud Defender suite Alert Logic Cloud Defender is a comprehensive suite of security software, including Threat Manager, Log Manager, and Web Security Manager. All customers that subscribe to one or more of the listed products will use the Alert Logic console. The suite is available for cloud environments, physical environments, and any hybrid environment.
Much of this information will be provided to you by your Deployment Services contact, and this guide is intended to supplement that guidance.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/get-started-console/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/get-started-console/</guid><description>Get Started with the Alert Logic Console The Alert Logic console provides a universal navigation experience for all Alert Logic customers, regardless of subscription level. The Alert Logic console displays only the tabs and pages appropriate to your subscription level. This topic describes all possible tabs and pages, but specifies the subscriptions that generate the tabs and pages.
You can check the operational status of the Alert Logic console in the Service Status page.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/get-started-google/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/get-started-google/</guid><description>Get started with Alert Logic Cloud Defender on Google Cloud Platform Alert Logic Cloud Defender is a comprehensive suite of security software, including Threat Manager, Log Manager, Web Security Manager, and Cloud Insight.
Alert Logic Cloud Insight is included with Cloud Defender for any Amazon Web Services (AWS) deployments. Cloud Insight is available only for AWS deployments, so it uses a separate portal. For more information about provisioning and usage of Cloud Insight, see Get Started with Cloud Insight.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/get-started-scans/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/get-started-scans/</guid><description>Get Started with Alert Logic Scans A scan detects and identifies network and host vulnerabilities in your environment. Scans can perform external attack simulations as well as comprehensive vulnerability checks including registry evaluation. For more information, see the detailed About Alert Logic Scans documentation. Alert Logic scans can also help you meet Payment Card Industry (PCI) compliance requirements. For more information, see Manage PCI Scans.
You can check the operational status of your automated and scheduled scans in the Service Status page in the Alert Logic console.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/get-started-tm-professional/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/get-started-tm-professional/</guid><description>Get Started with Threat Manager Professional Alert Logic Threat Manager Pro combines a cloud-based network intrusion detection system and a vulnerability assessment solution into a service that works in any environment, from on-premises to the cloud. For more information about Alert Logic subscriptions, see Alert Logic Subscription Levels. To learn more about your entitlements, see TM Professional Entitlement Summary.
Review system and platform requirements Before you get started, make sure all necessary parts of your environment are ready to be used with Alert LogicManaged Detection and Response.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/incidents-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/incidents-upgrade/</guid><description>Incidents Upgrade Alert Logic is upgrading customers to the new Alert Logic Incidents page with an enhanced and improved experience to maximize your ability to manage incidents. This upgrade enhances your experience, but still offers the same features and capabilities as the existing Incidents page.
The upgraded Incidents page continues to display information about incidents, how to use that information to manage and close incidents, and actionable steps to secure your environments.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/log-manager-pro-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/log-manager-pro-upgrade/</guid><description>Log Manager Pro Upgrade Alert Logic Log Manager collects, aggregates, and normalizes log data whether it originates in your own data center, a hosted environment, or the cloud. Flexible data collection options, including physical appliances, remote collectors with agents or without agents, and cloud native APIs, provide low-impact deployment options for all of your infrastructure. Alert Logic will upgrade Log Management customers to Log Management Pro, which includes a number of changes to your experience.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/log-review-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/log-review-upgrade/</guid><description>Log Review Upgrade Alert Logic is upgrading Log Review incidents with a new machine learning algorithms which allows Alert Logic to deliver a higher level of security value.
The Log Review machine learning algorithms can automatically detect many log-based incident types based on unique patterns and trends learned from your organization. Alert Logic analysts will still be involved in overseeing Log Review incidents, and the Log Review feature will continue to meet your log review compliance requirements.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/log-search-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/log-search-upgrade/</guid><description>Log Search Upgrade Alert Logic now offers an enhanced and improved experience for customers upgrading to the new Search feature. This document is intended to help you adapt from Log Search beta feature to the new Search feature.
The Search experience in the Alert Logic console allows you to perform basic and advanced searches for different data types. The Search feature is flexible for structuring your own search queries or using template, fields, and predefined expressions to help you find and organize messages most relevant to your investigation.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/notifications-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/notifications-upgrade/</guid><description>Notifications Upgrade Alert Logic upgraded the Notifications feature in Managed Detection and Response (MDR) to add new notification types. If you previously subscribed to incident or health status notifications in the Alert Logic console, your notifications are still active and sent to subscribed recipients.
For more information about the updated Notifications feature, see Notifications and Manage Notifications.
New notification types in MDR Alert Logic added two new types of notifications:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/omnibox-search-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/omnibox-search-upgrade/</guid><description>Cloud Defender Omnibox Search Upgrade Alert Logic now offers an enhanced and improved experience for Cloud Defender customers upgrading to the new Search feature. This document is intended to help you become familiar from Cloud Defender Omnibox search feature to the new Search feature.
The Search experience in the Alert Logic console allows you to perform basic and advanced searches for different data types. The Search feature is flexible for structuring your own search queries or using template, fields, and predefined expressions to help you find and organize messages most relevant to your investigation.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/pci-scans/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/pci-scans/</guid><description>Get Started with Alert Logic PCI Scans A PCI scan is a type of external scan used specifically for Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) compliance requirements. PCI scans offer a better assessment of web servers than the regular Alert Logic external scan, and produce a document that you can use as proof of compliance. For more information about scans, see Manage PCI Scans.
PCI scanning best practices When configuring your scans, use the following guidelines to create successful scans and scan results.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/professional/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/professional/</guid><description>Get Started with Your Alert Logic Professional Subscription Your account subscription dictates the level of protection you can assign assets in each deployment you create. You can create deployments for assets found in your Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Microsoft Azure cloud platforms, and from other cloud-based or physical data centers.
If you do not know which Alert Logic subscription you have, contact your account administrator.
For more information about Alert Logic subscriptions, see Alert Logic Subscription Levels.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/recommended-training/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/recommended-training/</guid><description>Recommended Training for New and Upgrading Customers Whether you are a new Alert Logic customer or you are upgrading from a legacy platform, Alert Logic recommends the following resources to learn about key features in Managed Detection and Response (MDR).
To access training videos, sign in to the Alert Logic console, select Support from the navigation menu, and then click Training to open Alert Logic University. You can then click links to the videos below to open them.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/scans-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/scans-upgrade/</guid><description>Scan Functionality Upgrade Alert Logic upgraded scan functionality to provide fully automated scanning for all your assets. You no longer have to create individual scans for every asset.
When you create a new deployment, Alert Logic automatically creates default scan schedules to perform external and internal vulnerability scans on all non-excluded assets and ports that vary according to deployment type. Alert Logic also creates a default discovery scan schedule to find new assets in Data Center deployments.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/scans/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/scans/</guid><description>Get Started with Alert Logic Scans A scan detects and identifies network and host vulnerabilities in your environment. Scans can perform external attack simulations as well as comprehensive vulnerability checks including registry evaluation. Alert Logic scans can also help you meet PCI compliance requirements. For more information, see the detailed About Alert Logic Scans documentation.
Scan types There are three types of supported scans:
Internal scans An internal scan runs from an Alert Logic appliance in your environment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/search-a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/search-a/</guid><description>Get Started with Search The Search experience in the Alert Logic console allows you to perform basic and advanced searches for different data types. The Search feature is flexible for structuring advanced search queries, and using fields and predefined expressions to help you find and organize messages most relevant to your investigation. Search now supports a variety of data sources that help you uncover potential threats and discover what data sources are present in an environment, and it provides tools for further investigation.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/search/</guid><description>Get Started with Search The Search experience in the Alert Logic console is intended to allows you to perform basic and advanced searches for different data types. The Search feature is flexible for structuring advanced search queries, and using fields and predefined expressions to help you find and organize messages most relevant to your investigation. Search now supports a variety of data sources that help you uncover potential threats, discover what data sources are present in an environment, and provide tools for further investigation further with the provided tools.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/subscriptions-addons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/subscriptions-addons/</guid><description>Get Started with Alert Logic Subscriptions and Add-ons Alert Logic MDR Essentials, Alert Logic MDR Professional, and Alert Logic MDR Enterprise are subscriptions for your Alert Logic customer account. Each subscription provides different levels of vulnerability and threat management services and capabilities for your on-premise, public cloud, or hosted data centers.
Alert Logic subscription levels Your subscription determines the level of protection you can assign for the assets in your deployments.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/subscriptions-revisions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/subscriptions-revisions/</guid><description>Get Started with Alert Logic Subscriptions and Add-ons Alert Logic MDR Essentials, Alert Logic MDR Professional, and Alert Logic MDR Enterprise are subscriptions for your Alert Logic customer account. Each subscription provides different levels of vulnerability and threat management services and capabilities for your on-premise, public cloud, or hosted data centers.
Alert Logic subscription levels Your subscription determines the level of protection you can assign for the assets in your deployments.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/threat-manager-pro-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/threat-manager-pro-upgrade/</guid><description>Threat Manager Professional Upgrade Alert Logic Threat Manager Professional combines a cloud-based network intrusion detection system and a vulnerability assessment solution into a service that works in any environment, from on-premises to the cloud. Threat Manager customers who choose to upgrade to Threat Manager Professional receive a number of changes that simplify and improve your experience.
The Alert Logic console shows only the tabs and pages appropriate to your product subscription.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/training-essentials-old/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/training-essentials-old/</guid><description>Training essentials Introduction to service How things work Managed services basics Operational UI walkthrough Allow 1.5 hours for the full operational orientation session, including the slide presentation. Please log into the Alert Logic console to follow along during the walkthrough.
Areas of the UI covered in this session: Users Service Status Support Information INCIDENTS tab SEARCH tab REPORTS tab CONFIGURATION tab Incidents Topics covered in this session include: Customer Accounts, User Accounts, and User Roles Multi-factor Authentication Service Status Reviewing an Incident Contacting the Alert Logic Security Operations Center (SOC) regarding a case or incident Log Review Cases Finding Unparsed Logs Notification Policies &amp;amp; Contacts Key Scheduled Reports Interactive Service Review Report Escalation Contacts Accessing Support Tickets Technical UI Walkthrough Allow 1.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/update-aws-roles-for-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/update-aws-roles-for-upgrade/</guid><description>Update AWS IAM Roles to Prepare for Upgrade This document is intended for customers with Alert Logic Cloud Insight, Alert Logic Cloud Insight Essentials, and Alert Logic Cloud Defender entitlements who are preparing to upgrade to Managed Detection and Response. Periodically, Alert Logic updates the policy documents used for the IAM roles that are required for Amazon Web Services (AWS) deployments. These updates, which Alert Logic announces in Alert Logic Console Release Notes, support new features and ensure your deployments continue to monitor your AWS assets.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/update-azure-deployments-for-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/update-azure-deployments-for-upgrade/</guid><description>Update Azure Deployment Configuration to Prepare for Upgrade This document is intended for customers with an Alert Logic Cloud Defender entitlement who are preparing to upgrade Microsoft Azure deployments to Managed Detection and Response. Prior to your upgrade to Managed Detection and Response, ensure your Azure deployments are configured properly.
Check for and fix Azure credential problems The most common issue with Azure deployments prior to upgrade is lack of credentials.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/upgrade-console/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/upgrade-console/</guid><description>Upgrade to Managed Detection and Response The Alert Logic console provides a universal navigation experience for all Alert Logic customers, regardless of your product subscriptions.
The Alert Logic console shows only the tabs and pages appropriate to your product subscription. This topic describes all possible tabs and pages, but specifies the subscriptions that generate the tabs and pages. For more information about subscriptions Alert Logic offers, see Get Started with Alert Logic Subscriptions and Add-ons.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/upgrade-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/upgrade-reports/</guid><description>Managed Detection and Response Reports Upgrade The Alert Logic Managed Detection and Response platform offers an enhanced and improved experience for customers upgrading from Cloud Defender, which includes upgrades to the Reports feature. This document is intended to help you find similar information from Cloud Defender Scheduled reports in the Managed Detection and Response Alert Logic console.
The Reports feature is available to all Managed Detection and Response product subscriptions. The Alert Logic console shows only the tabs and pages associated with your product subscription.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/upgrade-s3-collection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/get-started/upgrade-s3-collection/</guid><description>Upgrades to S3 collection in Managed Detection and Response This document is intended for customers with an Alert LogicAlert Logic Cloud Defender who are preparing to upgrade to Managed Detection and Response (MDR). Amazon Web Services (AWS) S3 collection performance, configuration, and efficacy have all been improved on the Managed Detection and Response (MDR) platform.
Upgrades to Performance The Cloud Defender S3 collection service used a poll-based mechanism to analyze objects in the S3 bucket, which required the repeated counting of all objects at the time of each poll.</description></item></channel></rss>