<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release-notes on Hugo documentation theme</title><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/</link><description>Recent content in Release-notes on Hugo documentation theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Designed by [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com) &amp; Developed by [Gethugothemes](https://gethugothemes.com)</copyright><atom:link href="https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/agent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/agent/</guid><description>Alert Logic Universal Agent release notes DO NOT INCLUDE RELEASE NOTES FOR APPLIANCES ONLY!
2021 ### Release date: November 4, 2021 - Agent Version 2.20.3
Bug Fixes Fixed possible non-Unicode characters in agent status and metadata (which can silently stall data collection) Fixed pollution of systemd journal with debug output from the agent Release date: October 21, 2021 - Agent Version 2.20.2 Bug Fixes Scan tools and updates directories are now properly cleaned on uninstall and reinstall Starting the remote syslog collector via /etc/init.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/alert-logic-console/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/alert-logic-console/</guid><description>Alert Logic Console Release Notes Alert Logic console release notes 2022 ### Release date: February ?, 2022
[Release note about the new Monthly Log Review Details report&amp;hellip;]
Alert Logic also released enhancements to scheduled reports:
For weekly and monthly report schedules, you can now schedule a report on a specific day of the week or month. A new Run Once option, available for non-interactive reports like the Monthly Log Review Details report, allows you to generate the report immediately instead of at a scheduled time.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/endpoints/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/endpoints/</guid><description>Alert Logic Extended Endpoint Protection Agent Release Notes Extended Endpoint Protection release notes 2021 ### Release date: Dec 01, 2021 Windows Agent Version 4.11.2.0
Bug Fixes Fixed one corner case where Kernel crashes. Release date: May 26, 2021 Mac Agent Version 4.12.0.0 Features Support for macOS BigSur version 11.x (automatic upgrade of Extended Endpoint Protection on macOS BigSur is not supported. The latest installer needs to be downloaded and installed manually to run Extended Endpoint Protection on BigSur).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/inline-waf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/inline-waf/</guid><description>Alert Logic Managed Web Application Firewall (WAF) Release Notes Alert Logic Managed Web Application Firewall (WAF) release notes Alert Logic supports the current version and the last two minor versions. For example, 4.5.1.0 is two versions behind 4.5.3.0, and an appliance running version 4.5.0.0 is unsupported.
Alert Logic does not automatically push new versions to customers, and an upgrade may be required if you need support on an older appliance.
2021 (4.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/maintenance-windows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/maintenance-windows/</guid><description>Alert Logic Maintenance Windows Alert Logic updates appliance software and makes product changes, as needed, within specific maintenance windows. Updates require no customer action or intervention.
Standard change window Alert Logic performs standard changes, which include those with lower risk profiles and should not interrupt your service, during the following hours:
US: Monday – Friday, 8 PM – 3 AM (Central Time) UK: Monday – Friday, 9 PM – 4 AM (UTC) Security content update window Alert Logic updates security content and signatures on the following weekly schedule:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/scanning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/scanning/</guid><description>Scanning Release Notes Scanning release notes 2021 ### Release date: November 17, 2021
Features Alert Logic released agent-based vulnerability scanning. Agent-based scanning enables users to leverage the vulnerability assessment coverage of authenticated network scanning without the need to manage credentials and with a reduction in network traffic and impact. To learn more, including how to enable this feature by deployment, see Agent-Based Scanning.
Release date: April 6, 2021 Features Alert Logic added an enhancement to your scope of protection capability for Data Center deployments.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/service-pack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/service-pack/</guid><description>Service Pack Release Notes Cloud Defender service pack release notes 2018 ### Release date: August 30, 2018
Bug fixes A lag in the PCI scan process has been fixed, preventing incorrect compliance scores from appearing early. Cloud Defender customers can now see all necessary information about GuardDuty incidents. Old links were removed from log message detail pages. Several minor fixes were made to the Incident page. Release date: August 14, 2018 Bug fixes The Events - Full and Top Signatures reports are only showing relevant signature information.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/template/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/template/</guid><description>Online release notes template This sample shows service pack release notes, but all categories should follow this format.
Release date: February 22, 2018 (UK); March 1, 2018 (US) Bug fixes This release fixes an issue where automatically closed disputes had the incorrect status of &amp;ldquo;Pending Review&amp;rdquo;. This was corrected and now automatically closed disputes have the status &amp;ldquo;Finished Failing&amp;rdquo;. This release fixes an issue where comments in the Overview page of Scan Dispute showed the customer name instead of the user name.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/web-security-manager-oob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://richg-github.github.io/docs.github.io/release-notes/web-security-manager-oob/</guid><description>Web Security Manager release notes Web Security Manager release notes Release date: April 9, 2018 Version 4.5.4.1-1501 Bug fixes Fixed issue displaying deny logs with malformed utf8 data
Resolve UI error related to IP sharding feature
Fixed grouping by country in the deny log dashboard
Stop logging at 10% free space left on Passive WAF
Read the correct core error log on auto-scaling masters
2017 ### Release date: December 11, 2017 Version 4.</description></item></channel></rss>